From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce get told, he goes unfold.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like be awake and step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like be awake and don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
And I've been missing in my sleep
I have a still story to tell you
I am still
I don't need it.
because, you know, Bita, I named the stream after her, right?
Bita's Biscuit, she doesn't like the Bita's Biscuit song.
I don't know why she doesn't like the Bita's Biscuit song.
It's really funny.
I don't know why she doesn't like it.
But you know what, I'll explain to you what had just happened.
I went, well, first of all, I woke up, I was taking a nap
and I just woke up to some very high-pitched voice
whining about, what was it?
Oh.
She was such talking about me and biscuits, right again, you know, she was so offended by the AI song. Oh
She was almost in tears over the stupid AI song, right?
I'll play this stupid song. I was like, it's a stupidest song.
She wants a diss track. I'll give her a diss track because you know what she just did. She's had she's timed me out in her chat
That was the first time she ever did that so and I never I didn't time around in my chat this morning
I let her say everything she wanted she named the fucking stream after me like well
She said you know I named so I did it back
What why is it okay for her to do everything and it's like if I do something and I'm like it
I'm everyone's evil everyone's mad. She you know she can do anything, right?
Okay. Oh, no, no, I'm sorry instant karma. I was looking I wasn't looking at the chat
I wasn't talking to anybody. I'm really distracted right now because of beta. Okay, just give me a second. Okay
Give me a second.
It's not a good time to like, you know,
we're gonna just hold it up, okay?
I'm trying to explain.
Vita is mad about some stupid biscuit song
when she's been torturing me with biscuits for months.
And then she's mad about, I make one stupid song, okay?
I'm gonna, so I'm gonna play it.
And I made another song too.
I'm gonna play that one.
She wants to play with me?
I'm gonna play with me, okay?
I'll either was be your friend, okay?
Fucking might you say anything you want
You did biscuits coming right up
Scooter hot pipe in a hot biscuit. Okay. I don't care. I don't care. I'm gonna super just as low as she is
Okay, I'm just as low. I'm gonna start when it's over reacting over every little fucking thing. She does about me
Okay, and she said it's what what did I do? What did I do to like to make yourself?
I mean
You know what she did
You know, but I actually like, you know, mine was good in nature and cute hers is just like trying to like, you know
She literally wants to make someone unalive themselves
It wouldn't happen, but it's just like she's trying to do
Crazy
Oh, she pissed me off.
What, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hide me in the chat, or just time me out, fine.
Time me out.
Oh, I can't say anything.
All I said was, you know, she got all mad about my song,
right?
But she can be over there.
And then she's like laughing like I'm overreacting, right?
Over it, right?
Oh, I wish I had her on tape overreacting because this is
Done these double standards. How about like, you know, we're all human beings
like
You know just protect, you know clean beta all times
Gee
I'm sick on I'll get to you, but where have we been we're in sick on where have you been if you first of all?
You've been gone for like months, right?
Can't see the chat right now. Okay, just give me a break. Hold on. I'm gonna say about something else
Fricking you this good song. It's ready
There you go, okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna take a minute a breath. Hold on
We're free. We're free a new song. So it's a good day. Okay a good day. Oh
Time me out and oh time me out
Wow, imagine if I had done that to her. I would never ever hear the end of that. I would never hear the end of it
I'm all over it. I'll go over it. Okay. So where's
The guys just remember
All I did was nothing and she and then all I said was like what but double standard
And she has her chat named after me. I can't even reply to the chat that's named after me. Does it make sense?
The whole chat is named after me. Well, not named after me. She didn't put my name in it. It just refers to me.
Oh, so maybe I said like month ago. Like it's like some relative thing, which is different.
Okay, so I can't see this chat. Let me just play the song and then I'll look at the chat and everything.
Just give me a break. Hold on.
Kind of a update.
It's a new biscuit song and since she asked for it. She asked for it
She said she said she said all biscuits are on the table. It's fun. It's fine. It's fine until I torture me with this good
So I think I saw a second one about
Here you go. Enjoy Eda
Yeah, yeah
The oven, you the smoke that won't stick
Your dough don't rise, cause you're getting too quick
Beat his biscuits, dry and bland
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
Claim you bring spice, but you bring in regret
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
Panna verse feast, we don't starve
Welcome to real lo-
Welcome to real.
How about another version of the song?
How about that?
Let's do another version.
I think it's calling out.
It wants to be played.
It's calling out to be played.
Please.
Play another Biscuit song.
Okay.
Let me be real mature about this.
Be real mature.
wow that made me feel a lot better
feel instantly better
how are you guys? hold on a second
I mean I'm done with double standards
aren't you done with double standards?
I don't like double standards, okay?
I really like single standards
Like that one
I'm gonna go to the chat in one second. I can't see it yet. Hold on just all
You came to the kitchen but forgot the recipe Serving up crumbs while I feast on legacy
I'm the fire in the oven you the smoke that won't stick
We don't starve on lies, your plate got nothing but re-hated fries, I'm the main course, truth
served hot, you're the snack that everyone-
We ain't finished yet
You came to the kitchen, but forgot the recipe
Serving up crumbs while I feast on legacy
Fire in the oven, you the smoke that won't stick
Your dough don't rise, cause your game too quick
Who feed us biscuits dry and bland
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
Claim you bring spice, but you bring in regret
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
Panel got receipts
She she she banned me from her chat. Okay. She banned me from her chat. Can you believe that?
What did I say? I said
What she's she's she's up there talking about biscuits and then she's crying about a biscuit song
She is the government
She
What's going on? I mean, it's insane. It's insane sanity. Yo
Trevor
Young man, how are you?
Yeah, how are you?
I'm doing good. Oh, let me close out the YouTubes here. I
Saw you dancing. I saw you dancing having a good time
On my butt a little bit
Yeah, I wanted to see butt cheeks, but
That's not on the agenda I get it
oh i got you brother that's fine that's fine look at you look at you like a little rock star
you know who you look like richard ashcroft have you you know the verb bitter sweet symphony
yeah yeah it's a bad the band richard ashcroft okay yeah the verb it's a bitter sweet symphony this
Yes, yes, you're Richard Ashcroft baby boy. You look better than Richard Ashcroft. You
look better than him.
Oh, you got a big screen TV
You're living the good life
Meanwhile, I'm living the bad life. No cats and I got no big screen TV
Hi Lenore
How you doing?
Lenore has never cared less in her life
Yeah, you see my little computer how big how small it is
What's that? I'm sorry. I didn't see it
Close the cat on it
That's your modem, right your Wi-Fi modem computer. That's the whole computer
That's the whole computer right there
That's your modem. It's like a tiny that's how big they are now
It's swear as my computer
Yeah, that's your modem, baby boy. That's your cable modem.
I don't have it. I have my modems over on the other side.
You're not fooling daddy on that one.
I think actually the modem is bigger than the computer.
It is actually called a Geekom mini PC.
And it was a good deal.
I'm not picking on Beta.
Beta first of all named her stream something like some reference to something I said before,
She said, I said, I'm Cable and she's a fool.
Hey, Syke, will you have me on the panel?
Well, I'm on the panel.
Can I?
You and Beter reminds me of my best friend
when I was in middle school and high school.
Her name was Zaina.
Her name was Zaina, a Bosnian girl.
And I was always like the little gate. Oh, Mr. Big Pikes forget about that story
We got Mr. Big Pikes on here. No, you're talking about Bosnia
Yeah, I know a bunch of Bosnia
Well, I was gonna tell the story about that, but then you came on the panel and showed me I'm chillin
No, I like go ahead. Yeah, they were here by the bus again. I want to hear about the Bosnian's
Okay real real real quick real quick real quick. So apparently I
It's like has this thing beta, but anyways growing up through what is she Bosnia high school?
I had my best friend
Mr. Big Pikes, do you really want to hear it?
Yeah, I do really want to hear it. I'm gonna hear about it. We'll figure it out
my best friend in middle school high school her name was Zana. She was from Bosnia and
I was always like the uh the uh the the cute little gay friend the cute little gay friend the best friend and we did everything together but the thing about females the thing about females is uh they actually tend to drift off to heterosexual males and when they do that and when they get knocked up
All of a sudden the little gay best friend becomes, uh, it's on the back burner.
It's on the back burner.
It's on the wheel.
All of a sudden, where did they get that?
But anyways, I want to hear about Mr. Big Pikes. Get on camera, Mr. Big Pikes.
Wait, so what high school did you go to?
You freaking stud.
Get on camera right now.
What high school did you go to at these Bosnians?
Oh, and Michigan? You wouldn't know?
Oh, okay, okay. Are you from Michigan, baby boy?
No, I've been to Eastland.
I've been to Eastland.
Oh, are you from Michigan?
No, I have a friend out there.
I
But I've gone out there like he's a streamer. I'm talking about a hassle nuts and good times
I wasn't actually talking about good times, but hassle nuts is the dude I hang out with out there hassle nuts
Yeah, he's a streamer too
I was trying to get him on here to like defend me one time, but
He wouldn't come
Best friend. Yeah, he's like he's busy pandering to like IP2 or something. They're trying to
He doesn't realize it's been here. I hear you. Mr. Bigpipes
So Trevor, do you know Mr. Bigpipes sent me to some dick pics of himself?
Do you really dude is this dude gay?
Is this gay?
Yes. All right. He's gay as shit like he's barking up the tree of the F-slurs. Oh
I'm a twink lover baby boy. Oh, I'm a twink. Oh, yeah show him the picture. Let's go
No, no, okay, okay, okay?
There's Alex in here. Hey Alex, what's up?
Oh shit. I'm sinning. I'm sinning Alex.
It's all male in there.
Is the girl you're being out with now?
Do you know Alexandra? Have you been Alexandra on the river?
I'm drunk Alex. I'm really drunk Alex, I'm sorry.
I think so. I think so. I think I'm more...
I just want to know like can you give me like an honest estimation of are you like of the
size maybe like who's that a bigger you are you big Trevor how big are you
I mean, oh, no, no, I was talking about me. I was talking about me, dude on the fucking
Fuck I have to go on Instagram
You're cute mr. Big Pikes mr. Big Pikes you I see
You on the RV remember remember when Saint fought dirty. He fought so fucking dirty. I didn't like that
I didn't care for that, Mr. Rick White.
Yeah, luckily, luckily I'm immune to eye gouges and, like, fighting like a bitch, so...
I robbed every mother fucker there like chicken Andy literally like
Like I wish that deleted shit would come back because it's like
Chicken Andy like open of the door on finds like what's up bitch and like fucking like cams like dude?
No, no in like whatever. It's like get the fuck out. He's like do you fucked up there?
I'm like fuck you dude all the RV driver can I remember him. I
Remember him
But yeah, whatever those motherfuckers. I still got a fucking pipe. I showed fucking
Yeah, I showed taking the fucking keys to RV and threw in the Mississippi River
And I take pride not being a snitch, you know, I handle my shit
Drinking and driving is that what's going on?
Yeah, dude like like saying was trying to say that like I was trying to give people my best bullshit like literally Jacob like checking
He's like yeah, like we won't like we want math and shit like ask him for the bar and stuff and
Jacob gave me fucking Adderall actually
What's going on psych is that you?
So, uh, but you want to go in there now? I was getting I was getting like sidetracked, huh?
No, like some other shady shit about those fucking like oh my god
Is that him? Wow at a boy. Oh my god legs of a salient. God damn
legs of a Mr. Bigfoot
Nothing wrong with that sir
Nothing wrong with that
You're a bit like a stallion big boy
Like I'm only six foot three. I'm only six foot three like
Oh, you're taller than I am it's like how tall are you?
We're gonna test the next time
Bro, Psyche, I love you. You look like you have your sunglasses.
He's all your glory. It's really the greatest thing ever.
Like a fucking gay schoolboy or some shit.
Well, I need a cute Japanese outfit.
I'm just wearing my pajama pants right now.
I think I'm having my feet are though.
Nice and comfy.
Ooh, look at those feet, look at those tutsies, look at those little baby tutsies, I love me
some tutsies, I love me some tutsies, oh look at those tutsies, look at those tutsies.
They make me puke dude.
Hey Mr. Repikes, can we see your tutsies baby boy, I want to see your tutsies, I love tutsies,
I love cute feet and I love little baby tutsies, that's what I love.
Like you're barking up. Why not the tree fights the wrong tree, okay?
Yeah, so I just want to say that I was I would say is hopefully this is like
She was talking about me all day. I went with a little piece flag and I was gonna say hi
Your auto is all fucked up now.
I was hidden in the chat.
Yeah, yeah.
You're back.
You're fixed.
Okay.
I was hidden in her chat.
Can you believe that?
I was hidden.
Like, I can't even have a voice in there anymore.
Well, hey, yeah, we can hear you now say, hey, listen, listen, you've created your own table.
You have your own platform.
You don't have to go into her chat and I'm not saying anything bad about her.
She can do her thing.
You can do yours and have your own channel.
You have your own audience.
So let her do.
She can do her thing.
You can do yours.
If I reacted the way she reacted tonight, and it's like, I'd be overreacted, or I'd be like,
or like, I timed her out in my chat.
She wasn't in my chat today.
I'd let her say everything she wanted to say, like, but I said one, literally said one thing
in her chat and I was timed out, and she was just like, you can't be.
You have a gay boy crush on her. You have a gay boy crush to where
you know, she was your friend and I think your feelings are hurt a little bit so where
It's kind of affecting you. I've been through that. I've been through that
Zana Zana the Bosnian girl who got knocked up and hit a bunch of kids
I went through the same thing
I'm not sure if Vita has kids or if she's ever been knocked up, but
But no, I'm just saying
Bro, I get it. I get it. But listen, you got your own platform. She has hers
You've created your own table of people who come to see you and hear what you say and she has her own people
So just do your own thing. That's all there is to it
We got well intertwined and then it's like
She oh hey, we ran though. So hey at least yeah, man. You like that job salmon
What happened is like she's
Overreacting or she's like saying stuff about biscuits when I go like about me and stuff
But when I did a biscuit song about her she's first of all she said I said that you know
It was about Iran and like it was offensive to Iran and it was about her cousin
No, that wasn't in the song
Like death to the unbelievers or something
Well, something like that, right?
I mean, it's like, this is called biscuit gate, OK, guys?
This is like, you know, I'll show my biscuits, OK?
This one?
That worked.
Oh, the tattoo, that's right.
That's right.
You can't ever outrun a man.
You have to be the 10 minutes.
I'm going to change it.
It's going to be biscuit.
So, um, this gets something, um, group, it's going to be the,
Oh, you got to do something about that now.
You got to do something.
I just have to figure out a new, a new, a new anagram.
I just need to figure out a new thing at the time.
Paulie, we'll figure it out.
Let me know a BKG.
Put the door.
I need a new, uh.
Yeah, I will.
I'm just going to change.
I'm going to change the door's name to, okay, BKG.
Thank you.
Hey, can I ask Mr. Redpikes, what do you feel about, I guess I ran, I ran is a big deal
between, oh look at the butt, look at the butt on site, you better fold those hammies
and undies down, so daddy Trevor can get a good look.
Oh shit.
I want to see some butt cheeks.
Ah, am I right Mr. Redpikes?
Am I right or am I wrong?
I'm chilling on that dude.
OK, I heard him.
Mr. Big Pipe, can you change your name to Mr. Biscuit?
That'd be kind of a challenge.
Mr. Big Stix?
Mr. Big Stix.
I don't know.
Oh, is he doing his car, Mr. Big Pipe?
I think, maybe.
You can you serenade Trevor?
Why can't he get on camera so we can all see? I don't know I begged him to go on
Hi
Oh my god
What are you doing?
Who is this young lady?
Wow, how beautiful.
No, I don't look beautiful right now.
Not right now.
This is Alex.
The Alex from that everyone knows.
Oh, wow.
Wow, you look beautiful, young lady.
Not at this moment.
No, I know
Lulu lemon stuff that I keep hearing about I I am I'm wearing a unit hard
That's what I'm wearing, and I have like this shirt shirt over it. I'm learning
This is my yoga wear. You got some yoga. This is my yoga outfit for the day. I had a good day
So you would say you're doing something you
Insight your partners. We're not partners
I like Psycholite and it seems to bother some people that I like him, but I'm going to keep liking him and there's nothing that I can do about that.
Psych, I thought you said you and Alex were doing something, some kind of podcast or...
We did.
Did I do that wrong?
No.
We did.
Oh, you did.
You did, okay.
Yeah.
I've also been, you know, we've been also, I've been checking in on her show and then, you know, she's been checking on my show and so we are, we're buddies.
It's just that, it's, everything is my fault and I'm just, I'm just gonna take responsibility, okay?
Everything's my fault. I tend to have a strong personality and that's all it is.
You know what, don't apologize because you know, you didn't do anything at all, at all wrong.
All you did was be a kind hearted person, like that's all you did.
All you did was like, just give me a chance, like I know what it is.
She's pretty, look how pretty she is.
What are you doing hanging out outside?
Yeah, I'm outside right now.
I agree.
There's some light and everything.
Very cool. And she's a pretty girl. You know about it. I'm kind of
Not really not really camping camping. I'm just
Very enjoying life, you know
More of the upscale camping
It is glamping. I'm not gonna say exactly where but I'm having I like being outside. I'm like an indoor outdoor cat
Seriously, I like where my cat goes
It hangs out with me. It's it's over here. That's where it is. It's over here right now
What's a girl you and if you don't mind me asking I'm in Michigan. What state are you in right now? I'm in California. Oh
You're in California. Oh site, too. He's a California boy
Mr. Big Pubs, what state are you in?
I'm in Michigan.
What state are you in?
I'm in St. Louis, Missouri.
St. Louis, Missouri.
Oh, you're in Missouri?
Okay.
Midwest.
Very cool.
This is my little buddy right here.
This is Lenore.
My little black cat.
My black cat.
That reminds me.
Huh?
My dad and his partner have this cat named, initially it was named Rascal, but they renamed
Looks just like that one striking eyes and max is bad. Oh max is bad. He's bad
But I like the black cats. We have like a lot of black cats throughout our family
We have everywhere this girl. She this girl is like her name's Lenore and she is like
Well today she came up and started kissing me like she's just like literally it comes and kisses me on the lips
You can kiss me
Aw.
You know, she covers the house all day, mostly, but she's been
pushing out a lot, but she's very, like, you know,
she's a very, very loyal cat, too.
I consider her my familiar because she's just, like,
everything was just, like, meant to be with her.
Aw.
And very, very sweet.
And the black cat's gonna bat a wrap because, you know...
they kind of actually the black cats um spiritually there's a lot of connotations to them that are good
And they are very protective and is that a black sigmes or is it just like you don't know?
I don't know, but yeah, she was found in like a parking lot like and like the cat rescue lady was like looking for a black cat
And then she went to work. There's a cat in her parking lot at work
but a little
Cage for it and came out a couple hours later and
Little nor was in the cage and then she brought her over to my house that night and
Pictures of her kiss it like it was just a kitten right and she was like she was like huggy
We were just hugging embracing it again. I was so sweet and she's just been so
like she's such a loving cat, I've never had a cat kiss me like that so it's like she just doesn't know at all.
He loves him.
She does.
Hey friends, I got to go before the liquor store closes. Hey Alex, it was nice to see you, I'm a fan of yours.
You're so pretty, you are so pretty.
You are so pretty.
And that sight you have to love you, you're a rock star.
Mr. Big Pipe, you stud, you absolute stud.
Well, thanks, you guys.
I'll see you.
Thank you, Trevor.
You have a good night.
All right.
I was born that way.
Yeah.
I think we're just naturally gorgeous people.
You could just say thank you.
You could just say thank you, Mr. McFly.
I mean, I'm going to say it's like, I don't know,
it's genetics or some shit.
You know you're good-looking Mr. Big Pipe, so you kind of have that star quality look to you, kind of like a, you know, your kiss level.
I'm just saying, I don't know.
You're like a freak.
He's a rock star. He's a rock star. He just is.
Yep, and I am.
No, Mr. Big Pipes and I we had our ups and downs, but I think we're up. We're on an ups plane
We're done, right? Big pipes. I just took another like shot
Every time he comes back around it's always on the up. That's just his nature
I don't want to be too much of a rock star. I gotta like fit in
Why that's boring no one's like no people are like recognized
It's sinking into it.
Let's just be famous.
Eventually we'll be so famous we have to get security to keep people away.
Well, you gotta be good though.
You gotta be able to back it up.
You already are at that level of...
Oh, like...
No, I'm not.
Mikey is at that level.
I have your security guards.
It's crazy.
I got two doorknocks today of Grubhub.
Really?
Yeah. Did anyone pay for the food at least? No, never. Never.
The only thing they paid for was the bags of a manure.
They paid for like the two dollar bags of the manure, but they didn't pay for any of the ore grub hubs.
People sent you manure? Yeah. 50 pounds of it on my doorstep.
I mean, it wasn't plastic bags, but I mean, it was just...
And it's like this shit people would do to like King Cobra, and he's dead, no?
Well, that's not very nice.
I mean, it's like, you know, I don't know what happened to him, but, you know, I think
he like got pushed over the edge a little bit, and so you're sad at the moment.
I agree.
I'm doing that.
Because he was like, obviously he was a little bit like autistic or something, but he has
hit them kind of mental thing going on a little bit, but I don't think he was a bad person,
Picked on it's like hard for yeah, and his dad said you know after the the morning after he died
That like he just had a kind of neon sign that said bully me on
Oh, the time he was a kid. Oh, really?
Well, yeah, he was one of those easy easy targets, you know, and it's like that's so sad that people like
I like to say go pick on someone on your own side, pick on somebody either of your own mental capacity or smarter than you.
Why go after somebody that doesn't even have the social skills to understand?
I'll tell you why.
Adrenaline rush.
Let's say your life is boring.
Normally you would watch TV or a movie maybe look at stuff on YouTube, but then you discover
That suddenly you can affect people's lives who are real people you get the immediate reaction
It's mainly gamers who get into the trolling. You know, I was talking to
Someone in my family who's younger than I am about it. It's like and he was mature gamer mentality
Yeah, the gamers, the gamers, they call each other FACT viewers.
They're stuck in that age, they're stuck in that age, which is the issue, and that leads to other issues.
Well, they don't realize that the streamers are not a game.
I mean, if you want to look at it as a game, it can be a game, but it's real people.
And I think that people get caught up in it.
that's what they came out of these these gaming communities like even like the
squatting and everything that was originally done to like people on you
know Call of Duty or something like that in the point which out of Call of Duty
they would squat or
Predators and like they would or people would like pretend to be an admin and stuff and I don't it's like a lot of stuff
But it's trickled over into the TV community first place
I saw the discord all the gamers are on discord
They're looking for a new high because the gaming is a digital high
You do get that serotonin, you know that rush that adrenaline and whatnot in your mind
Did you ever see 90 day fiancee?
So that was what I was watching, that's the only TV show I was watching a couple of years
ago and so all I was watching on YouTube I was watching terror readings and I was watching
Manny de Fiance stuff, like the commentators and so there's a guy named John Yates that
does this show and he's a gay guy but he started doing shows about, they stumbled upon these
Um, and there are these private groups and it was like they are sharing like other people's like kids schools
Kids photos. That's what happened to control up. No, no, I'm so glad you brought that up
That's exactly what big troll has been contending with for the past at least
five years at least
That's what it is. It's all in that discord.
And when you have kids, imagine how easy it is to control with my cats and stuff like that.
But people that have kids, it's very easy to...
But it's like, but then they're going way too far with like, doxing of their kids and stuff like that.
It doesn't make sense. But it's like, it happens even like in a, like a silly, like, you know, 90 Day Fiance is kind of a silly show.
But it's like, it's about, it's about the control. It's about people wanting to control what they can't control in their actual life.
I mean, I first saw it when I left the adult industry.
That's when it got really bad for a lot of people.
Some people did kill themselves.
You can ask Justine about that.
She knows a few girls they did.
Like the one guy you did.
I remember the-
I don't know if you feel as bad as possible.
There is like some kind of like there's a couple scandals in the adult industry wasn't there over like
Like the bear back stuff or like and then I remember there's like a proposition in like Los Angeles or like California about yeah
They changed a lot of the protocols. They made it to where it's a lot safer than it used to be
I mean when I went in, I mean they lied to us. Oh, they lied
they acted like everything was safe and super great and I mean for what it was, it was, but
it got, people got greedy. I think that's really what happened, people got greedy.
So things had to shift, change. That happened, and it's like, right, and that's kind of like,
Just reminds me of Michael Jackson a little bit when he like he offered one of the mothers of the Wade Robb. Yes
You offer like $200,000 to let her son like go alone to tour the country with them and be a backup dancer on the stage and stuff like that
Just for her to like, you know
It's very easy because they're flying them out from Australia. They're like they're they're not very wealthy
You know, they're very you're kind of poor or yeah
Basically, you know
When you have when you have that kind of money and power is it's like a little bit of a money
Money rules this world. Unfortunately. It just does
If you have enough money, you can get a lot not everybody
But you can get a lot of people to do a lot of things that they normally wouldn't do
So yeah, I mean wow, it's like really like and bad bad things, too
It's like there's a certain thing that wouldn't do for a billion dollars, right?
It's like I have you know, but I just think they're just like against
Doesn't take a million dollars for a lot of people. It's it's a few thousand. Yeah
So it's that I mean, but that's why I think what with whatever we have we should be we should be
Happy with what we have and we do have a lot. I mean, it's like, you know, as you know the Americans like we have
Even like the least wealthy American
It's better often more than yeah
But it's good to want more is because I mean, that's what keeps you going
That's what keeps you, you know pushing for more and wanting more
Kind of like when I say like the luck like money is not evil. It's the love of money over
Because money is like it's not even like this physical world. It's like, you know, it's very temporary and we can't take anything with us
It's like all of it's like it's all
No, well, they're gonna agrees to agrees to it right there else
It's like it's just paper printed paper with the thing that has no value when countries go bankrupt and stuff like that
They use the the money for fire fire kindling, right?
They're burning them just because they were so cold they had to burn the dollar bills and
The value of them is firewood at that time. So
Yeah, I mean money is energy
Ideally, you know, it's like, okay. I did this amount of work
So for this amount of work, I should get food
shelter
entertainment
health
care of some sort
or something but
So did you hear about what happened today with that young man who was basically assassinated?
His name was Charlie...
Charlie Kirk.
He...
I remember when he first came out because I was a big fan of Candace Owens for a while.
at one point were, you know, doing speaking engagements together, and I didn't agree with a lot of what he had to say, but there were some things, but he had so many, that's why I say, you know, you got to take certain things seriously when people say things to you, because you might not think that the worst of the worst, which is what happened to him, could happen, but it could.
You know track to be a politician and whatnot
And somebody decided to just take them out and they did I heard you say today like you said like his
Demographic is like a lot of people that maybe are like
In these communities, yes, and like and so I got a call today from my Russian friend
And she's like in this like you know program right now after after she got out of prison
She's in this program for you know GD and saying this house and everything
But she called almost in tears over this Charlie Kirk thing and she oh really she's like oh my god
She's like he's so nearly about it. Yeah, she knew about you know all about it
I think she might have showed me him before or something like that
But she was like oh, he's so brilliant and he's this conservative like I was like
I never had really heard about him, but I might have before, but here was the problem. Okay. Not him.
It has to do with everything revolving around Republican. Now, when Trump first came out,
and I was listening to some things that he had to say, and people around him more so than him,
I did switch parties from Democrat to Republican. I'm still a registered Republican.
But I didn't realize so many other things came with that that I don't agree with
So, I mean a lot of people such as myself Blacks African Americans
We did switch because you know, we were listening to
Candace Owens the people around her and we were you know, a lot of us have been thinking for a long time
You know why by default?
Should we align with a certain party if we don't agree with everything in that party?
But it's gotten to where it's almost become like defensive voting because of certain things that have happened.
So, I don't know.
Let me get my battery from my phone in California
Republicans are like a lot different from you know, Southern Republicans, right? It's like and it's like I would I would I would say so
Because my my uh, my parent like you know, I was always basically when I got political in the high school
And I'm not really good at it more, but I was always very into the libertarian party
Because I just love I like I like the idea of
socially liberal and like you know decriminalization of a lot of a lot of
these victimless crimes and as well as more economically conservative like
that I like that part of like the Republicans but I don't like the social
you know anti-gay stuff but it's like they're really not that anti-gay in
California for the most part of victimism.
For the most part, I don't think much of anyone is truly anti-gay. I mean,
it's always a threat, okay? You know, growing up in the environment that I grew up in,
especially being very close to my dad, I am very aware of certain dangers. There are some people
who don't think that I should even exist, and they have told me not to, I've never had anyone
say it to me to my face, but I've had people online say it to me because they don't think
And especially within, you know, the African American and Black culture, there's a thing
to where, especially the men, they're like, oh, if a woman is a Black woman and she ends
up with a guy who is LGBTQ, then, you know, both of them, they should just be burnt at
the stake, basically.
I mean, seriously, that's a certain mentality.
And I had to deal with a lot of that just growing up.
It's ridiculous.
You wouldn't think, but it's true.
And that's why when I was talking to your friend,
Summer a little earlier, but I think we're backstage.
I don't think anyone heard it.
But I was telling her that, you know,
I consider myself to be very, very, very straight,
I've always been in the LGBTQ world from family to working in the adult industry to outside of that
That's just me. I might as well be if I could be I
Don't there needs to be another letter
You know, maybe LGBTQ
See children of people who are LGBTQ there needs to be a C at the end
As A-Straight allies or something like that?
Yes, because we exist, but we're not supposed to exist.
It's a very interesting phenomenon.
I have a sibling who's definitely, she never talks about this.
She gets mad at me because I do talk about it,
but it's a part of our life, and I'm not ashamed.
No one should be a shit. It's like I think that's why like I want to focus on the interracial relationships because at one point in time
That was what gay is today
It just is and it still isn't in some culture some people
Some people will prefer to be around people who are in a monoracial
LGBTQ
that's crazy. Yeah. The racial, they're, they're about, oh my gosh, they think it's like something
wrong with it. There's nothing bad about mixing the races and stuff like that. But I think,
isn't it, aren't the races kind of, they'll think about stronger, like they're,
well, I think that I think multiracial people are the most beautiful people. I am biased because I
have a lot of younger relatives who are all multiracial people. They are all very intelligent,
I have a cousin who just finished law school and she's multi-racial and she had a hard
time for a while because of some things, but I was even telling her, I'm like, yeah,
you know, I'm switching gears.
I want to talk about that.
And she's like, please do.
And I was like, are you serious?
Most people say, you know, don't.
And she's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, you need to because you saw it firsthand.
You saw a lot.
So I will.
People now that are like and even the people you wouldn't even be able to tell that we have the DNA tests and things like that
So people can see it like I think there was some guy that was on more
I think a Jerry Springer or something like that and he was very racist
And then they ended up giving him a DNA test and he was like 10% black or something like that
And you know it's like it is the key or he had some some mixed in and right and you would never know sometimes but
A lot of people that you think are white are not as white as you think that they are a lot of people that are black are not as black as you think they are for any any ethnicity sometimes when especially when a person is half black and half Asian or half white and half Asian, you don't even know.
You think that maybe that there's just like an exotic quality about them.
very cruel
Yeah, I mean it's like but uh
Yeah, I think that they are I think it's a perfect time to be doing this because I think that there's so many children of the
Couples now, and I think that that's the direction the future is going
It's where we're all gonna have it's like no one's gonna get offended by anything because we're all gonna have a mix of everything
Basically inside of us. I am praying that that's the case. I really am because I
When I when I think about
Just certain situations. There's this girl that I met when I first got out to California
Years ago when I when I was first in the adult industry
Beautiful she went by the name Sophia. She kind of like Mariah Carey and
She was half black half white
As soon as she got to California the agents were like, okay, we're gonna label you a Latina
Because that's how she could get more work. She didn't speak any Spanish though
Interesting, but she was one of I'm not gonna say what her stage name ended up being but she became incredibly popular
Because she actually did have a perfect
stereotypical Latina look, but she was never she was not Latina
Yeah
Remember Rachel doze out. I think she was like in Washington. Yeah. Yeah, we all know about her
Do you know?
Do you know about new kazoos? I
Did an interview with him?
He was one who just he decided he wanted to be black, but then he became white again
Because the Milano tan, that's how he was darkening his skin. It's like a chemical that you inject yourself with. Oh
Killing him. Oh shit. I had this killing his liver
See, yeah, this lady right here. I'll show you this little short video. So this woman is
Did a similar thing?
And let me see where I find and
You will be a little bit shocked. This is a little bit shocking, but
first best video, okay
Yeah, here's a little, little clip here. Here we go. Um, share screen. Oh, I've seen that.
I've seen that. They call it, um, black fishing when people pretend to be black, but they're
My makeup color was 10. Yes, and now I'm out of the limits
I I had in January I had three injections three injections in January my doctor gave me them in the belly
I know they had to be one day a little scrunch. Yes, then a little bit more the next day
And then a little bit more at the third day. Maybe he gave you one too much. No, no
No, I like this color. Yeah, well that's good. I mean is it different you could be toast color or you could be burnt toast
But we've got listen
Crispy right crispy. Okay
Okay, that was a little racist actually
Yeah, that was racist
That was I mean she's basically the color. I am okay. She achieved it
She achieved it. I mean, well, here's what I will wonder. You know how I got hurt, right? Let me show you
It's healing. It's healing. I don't you know, but what's what would you say?
So every part of me is Burt and that's supposed to be regular. No
Yeah, that's it. That's that's
That's it a Lego or no, I scraped when I fell off my e-scooter I scraped the skin off
It's gonna take it. No, it doesn't it doesn't hurt. It's just that the coloring hasn't come back. It's gonna take at least
It's probably gonna take about four months
Cuz I'm pretty dark. Oh, unless I've been out in the sun for the summer
But I shift a lot. If I'm not in any sign, I can get very light, but I prefer to be dark.
I look better. I look slimmer, too.
And that's the goal, because you can never be too rich or too thin.
I like that quote.
Also, you know, there are many benefits. I think like darker skin is like, you know, they have like less skin cancers and things like that, right?
Also, the aging process is a little slow.
Black don't crack, right?
I've heard that.
I don't want it to crack.
I think I'm cracking a little bit, but I, you know,
there's girls that I went to college with and whatnot.
And there's the difference,
but it's not a nominal difference.
It's just, you know, everyone has, you know,
some people have beautiful, beautiful hair.
Some people have beautiful bodies.
Some people have beautiful skin, beautiful eyes.
Partly anybody has all of it, you know, right?
Well, yeah, everybody has some kind of like insecurity, right? And that's like, yeah
because uh
Human bodies, you know, it's like they're very interesting. I guess there's a lot of variations in it. Let's just say there's yeah
Well, look at okay, so they also scraped over here now. This is almost brown again. This is gonna take a little bit
But, I mean, the big part, I mean, it's like, it just takes a while for things to heal.
But I was saying that, I think that was my spiritual lesson because I was hurting so
much internally.
I needed some external pain.
It did release some stuff, so that's life, you know?
Yeah, well, that's the thing it's like there's like those people that will do things like self-injury and stuff like that because that is like some kind of
But there's better but there's ways like you know some I think summer was
said that she, that's why she started tattooing,
it's like so much, because it was like a way to channel
that into like something that was turned into
like a beautiful result rather than, you know,
some kind of small-
Well, I've decided if this does not come back
the way it should, I think it will,
because the accident just happened like a month ago, okay?
But if it's, you know, not the same,
that's gonna be where I get my first tattoo.
Cool. Why not and I all in you know, it's funny
I always said to myself if I were to get a tattoo it would be a sleeve sort of thing
So if the coloring doesn't come back right the color from the tattoo will really pop. Yeah, so
You know, maybe that's just
You know some sort of spiritual lesson for me saying, you know, maybe you do need a tattoo. The question is what would I get?
I don't know
I think something happened to do with like a cross and a sun and maybe like an orchid
Something like that. They're like orchids
Like the gods next time
Or the sublime son
I've never had a tattoo, so it would be my first tattoo.
You have no tattoos.
I have zero tattoos.
That's why I got a lot of work when I was in the adult industry, because I have zero
tattoos.
Look at that tattooing.
That was a thing back then.
Now it's like tattoos are kind of like the standard that I feel.
Yeah, I just, I didn't want to.
That's kind of the alt girl look now.
That's the new thing now, like full tattooing.
That's like raging against the machine, like crazy.
That's a lot of tattoo right there.
People do the whole body.
Yeah, these ones are kind of crazy.
There's people that, yeah, they're doing,
I think Machine Gun Kelly did it or something,
or somebody that did it.
I'll try to fix that.
No jumper he's he's like not his entire body is just like
Like what happens when you run out of space?
Right, then what are you gonna do the first time I saw a tattoo like that was from on the base player for rage against machine
Adam Grammys in it from a no jumper is Tim Comerford
Yeah, oh who is who? Oh, yeah, I'm rigid machine, but uh, the guy out from uh
He like he like sleeps with other guys with his wife
Yeah, that's the guy. I think that's no jumper guy
His trip mac is one of the contestants, but yeah, yeah, yeah, you don't want to be in a relationship like that
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
If a man is too into your looks, he most likely is like that, and he just wants to watch.
You don't want that. Stay away. Stay away.
I don't know if I know. I'm chilling now.
You know what's really popular is like...
Like if I'm in love with this one now.
Like these white guys with like kind of a small pee pee and like having their white foot with big black eyes.
Like I can't relate to that.
You can't relate to that. It's a big fight. I don't know.
So then it's like, what's like, I don't know, if you're like a size queen, I don't know, like...
You're big, you're really big anyway, so it's like, you're not going to be hard to find someone.
I got some Uber Eats on the way, and then I'll drink some more.
Well, I had my McDonald's, and I had a double chicken box.
I had a good uh, I had a good little lunch, but I woke up. Yeah
I've been um in the outdoors all day. I'm feeling great. I'm feeling tired. I feel good. I feel like I feel new
That's what I like about
Being in nature. I got to find more nature
Like I'm kind of doing baby steps more and more into nature. Eventually. I might be off for it
I might yeah, you could do a weekend with me at a music festival. I'm sure like these men know you want to do that
I know you do you're like we'll do it civilization
Yeah, well, I mean out here. I mean where I am right now
Where I am right now I can I can actually see some people and I know that they're party people
And all I got to do was hop over that fence.
No, no.
I might later tonight.
You never know.
But, um...
Like, imagine if you had a banjo and a harmonica.
So much.
Well, did you have that view there?
You know what?
I gotta get a harmonica again at least.
At least.
I'm thinking about picking up the guitar again.
That's what I'm thinking about doing,
just because it would be more convenient in the keyboard.
That keyboard, I'm too old to be hearing that set around.
Well, you're really good on the keyboard.
I love like, you know, the music,
I love like the sound of it.
I wish I could play piano better.
I took lessons for a few years, but I didn't really play it.
You would be great because you have long fingers.
Yeah.
So you're meant to play either guitar or piano.
Either one yeah, I actually don't have long fingers. I have an instrument. I'll show you
Oh, I know what he's got. He's got a tone a tone drum. I've seen him. I've seen him use it
He's got the UFO looking tones around if that's what I'm thinking that he's gonna bring
It's like a pan. It's a pan. It's like a pan drum. Yeah, those are sweet. I think he's got one
Here that I have right here, this is my...
What's the key?
A few years ago.
Is it a pan?
Is it a pans rum?
No.
Oh, that's a good one.
Oh!
Dude, that's almost what I said.
I almost said some weird, like, leers.
Yeah!
It's a free string.
It has free strings.
It has a bow, but it's like the bow you need to put this wax on it.
And I haven't figured out really how to put it on right.
Like, you could have a sound, but...
Like, tune it up.
It's a beautiful instrument, though.
It's beautiful, and I really love it.
You know what, tomorrow night, or the next night, I'll have my keyboard set up again,
because I'm in a different place again, and I'll try to set it up again, but...
We can jam.
Yeah, I'd love to try it.
I have the drum, too.
I have a drum around it, because a steel drum,
I have plenty of holes in it.
I know you got that steel drum.
I saw you with the steel.
It's like a UFO-shaped drum, right?
I saw you with it one day.
Yeah, I want one of those.
Yeah, I wish I could play it better.
It has little things on it.
You can push numbers on it, and you hit the numbers and stuff.
So if I knew the numbers, it wouldn't.
forget the numbers, use your intuition, you don't need the numbers, you just whatever
sounds good is what you want, that's how that is.
I wish I had some more weed, then I could, it's always fun to jam on it from your own
side.
I wish I could give you some, because I have plenty, I'm going to go right now and get
a joint.
It just, it just is because I have been indulging in just nature cannabis, a little hard cider
cigarette, and that's all I need.
Also, a lot of lamb, I've been eating lamb.
Yes, I love that.
Yeah.
Lamb is just a hit.
over here I got a propane fire pit so I don't got to worry about the firewood
yeah well the place I was before the host loved me because I was like oh I'm
gonna leave this for your next guess but they had a bunch of stuff that I didn't
use and they were like are you the guest or are we the guest and I'm like you
tell me I don't know
Yeah, I wish I could play instruments, but I'm like, you know, I am like, I'm really good at like music and like, like, uh, like, uh,
I know that like the sound of music and stuff like that. I think I'm pretty good with the AI music, too.
You are. You're really good with the AI music.
I love that song. I mean, that song that you made for me, that, um, what's it called, Neon Goddess or Neon Empress, something like that?
If I could disconnect it, I'll reconnect because my phone battery is probably gonna run out
Yeah, and I like the Alexander songs too
I love it
I don't know some of the songs I kind of recognize the sound of some of the songs from other songs maybe
They well, they're based on that's how AI works
It's based that's why so many musicians are pissed. I mean, you know, I was talking to this girl
I know she's been a recording artist forever and she was telling me and she was like, so what am I supposed to do now?
And I was just like, you know, you're gonna have to adapt
And she was she was crying
She was like, I don't know.
Nobody wants to, you know, the AI.
And I was like, well, you know, find how the AI is going
to amplify.
It's going to be the people that can play instruments
are going to be more in demand and like live.
Well, that's like what I was going to say.
It's like, like player pianos and jukeboxes have existed.
Yeah.
It's not going to.
Yeah, even like what people might have thought, oh my god,
a CD player, there's music playing,
and the band's not even there, you know.
It's like, of course, they cut the people into it, right?
But it's like, you know, there is, I mean, and also people complain about AI.
I'm sure that AI has been in the music industry for quite a while.
You know, there's been the auto tune and like, you know.
Nobody talked about it.
I mean, there's so much you can talk about it, it's a secret.
There's, you know, we remember really vanilla, right?
Like in their work.
Oh yeah.
Girl, you know it's true.
Yeah, it's great that some people have the look and it's like really about it.
It's all about the look.
The look is more important, unfortunately, than the talent.
If you got both, fuck it.
You're golden, but a lot of people don't.
I'm going to reconnect.
I got to log into my other phone. I'll be back.
Okay, so I'll play the Alexander song, Alexander song, Mr. Big Pipes.
Charging up her laser.
Here's the Alexander song. It's called Alexander.
And?
Can I jam along?
Yeah, of course you can.
Okay.
I got some freaking Uber Eats on the way, dude.
I'm gonna drink some.
Okay, download.
So, A.L.
Tacos.
I think it's this one. Here you go.
So here's the song. This is the Alexandra song.
Let's go and check it.
Where the real begins, she's gorgeous, she's witty, got fire in her eyes
Smart and vivacious, where laughter flies
She's a goddess in the glow, high priestess on the screen
Words like lightning strike, honest and serene
Mystery and kindness, wrapped in every line
Generous of spirit, a star that truly shines
She'll joke on her trolls, let the script with flare
A vivacious queen, with a knowing stare
Her watchers see the magic in her fearless way
She's weaving truth and humor through the everyday
She's a goddess in the glow
High priestess on the screen
Words like light and strike, honest and serene
Mystery and kindness, wrapped in every line
Generous of spirit, a star that truly shines
She'll joke on the trolls, get the script with flair
A vivacious queen with an old man stare
Her watchers see the magic in her fearless way
She's weaving truth and humor through the everyday
She's a goddess in the glow
High priestess on the screen
Generous of spirit, a star that truly shines
Alexandra, Alexandra, laughter in her heart
Every headline is hushed with a raven heart
Funny and fearless, a melody that states
She's the light in the labyrinth, the fire
So here's to the queen of IRL nights
Turn news into wonder
And roms in her eyes
With kindness and wit
She'll carry us far
Our goddess, our priestess
Our bright shining star
Yeah
Um, you know, are you done with the good fights or are you good?
Yeah, I'm chillin' with that.
Okay, I have one more.
Uh, this is Neon Priestess.
I'm gonna give my Uber Eats.
I'll take a couple more shots.
Okay, dope.
I'll put this song on and then...
Well, it's not here yet.
Okay, here you go.
Bye.
the kitchen but forgot the recipe serving up crumbs while i feast on legacy i'm the fire in
the oven you the smoke that won't stick your dough don't rise because you're game too quick
what's gonna find it what happened to the music
Oh, the moon is huge!
Let me show y'all.
That's the moon, fuck.
That's a man.
That's a blood moon.
It says the moon. It's huge tonight. I wish you could see it like the way I see it because it's
The first time is crazy.
It's pretty big, yeah.
For Capricorn, prepare for a tidal wave of opportunity
to connect and learn all, and off the charts,
cerebral energy, because the blood moon
is happening in your third house of communication.
You'll feel like you're buzzing with ideas
for collaboration with friends.
You're going to pick up new skills
and have eye-opening experiences,
perhaps by planning a weekend getaway.
Allow your imagination to run wild
to the stage for success and connection.
So that's a capricorn. What's your sign, Mr. Big Pipes?
Uh, what am I? Like a Libra?
Your Libra? Okay, so you're an air sign. Libra, it says...
Super peel.
I'm on the couch.
What's your birthday?
Yeah, I don't want to say it okay, but it's it figured out me in general
Third week of October
No, it's a Libra
Yeah
So anyway, I'll read Libra that relationship through teaming and experiences that aren't in sync with your greater purpose or sense of inner peace
On the chopping block because the luminous lips is hitting your sick cows are wellness and everyday hustle
you're no stranger to putting your needs on the backburner in order to promote harmony,
but you're called to acknowledge and tend to your needs on a more regular day-to-day basis now.
As a result, you can look forward to a greater sense of balance and both being.
Does that make sense for you? If anyone wants me to read their sign, just mention it in the chat
off. I'll read it because it hears you. You know, it's one such thing interesting though,
they're like, you know, modern astrology is not really based on the stars as much as any
It's based on the equinoxes and the solstices, right?
It's put into the core statements of the chart,
and that's across the solar cross on the chart.
It's like the core statements of the season.
And it was kind of interesting, because the thing
about astrology being out of stars,
but it's really not the season, I think,
along the Capricorn's winter.
We're born in the darkest time of the year, actually.
We're born right in the middle of winter.
the middle of winter, it was the darkest time of the year.
And we're as light as four in the dark, right?
As you think.
People around our birthday are special people.
Howard Stern is, let's see, who else?
And Elvis Presley is right around our birthday.
David Bowie is right around our birthday.
Nicholas Cage is our birthday.
Yeah, Nicholas Cage is January 7th.
And I think David Bowie is January 8th.
I think Elvis Presley is January 8th also.
and then Meryl Nantz is going to do it.
Valentine's, baby, this or something.
Oh, Valentine's Day.
Oh, hey, Jim Nick.
How are you?
So we are at Jim Nick.
I saw it.
Hey, Jim Nick.
I woke up, and Jim Nick was in the VIAs.
And Jim Nick, pretty songs.
Jim Nick, you're always welcome here.
And I didn't tell him.
I didn't say, like, he just said,
God, if David couldn't come here,
I never took that.
other people, but I think Jim Nick often though, and I really, I know Jim Nick since I started
streaming basically, right?
He met on a, she told, she did, she said she can't come here, okay, wow.
When did you start streaming?
He did block, he did block me in her chat tonight, so I couldn't, I said one thing and
then I was blocked.
I've never been blocked before, I was kind of shocked, I know I shouldn't have been like
I was just talking about me and stuff and so I got the biscuits and I was like hey
She can make fun of me about biscuits. I can why she's so mad at the song
I'll just stay away. I was to do it. She blocked me for being your mod tonight. Oh jar jar
Guys it's turning into a pretty nasty isn't that getting I'm not gonna block her
Alex bring us back on the rails we're going off the rails here no you're not
you're not I'm just it's gonna blow over I'm going off the rails I like I need
it's gonna blow over I'll be sick I got I got food on the way I just took a
I don't even have anything against Alec that's called me the usual because she mentioned her and she didn't say anything.
Oh, well, I would just suggest that maybe, you know, to Jim Nick, don't say anything about me, okay?
And to everybody, pretend like I don't exist,
because I actually have been trying to take steps back.
Certain things draw me back,
but pretend like I don't exist
because my intention is not to cause any strife or hurt
or anything like that.
I don't think you said that you're not meeting that in a cool way or anything, you're saying
that you get pulled back into situations sometimes.
I do.
And I have to learn to put more boundaries up myself.
That's what I'm realizing I have to do.
So I'm doing it.
hurt them unjustly. I do apologize. I don't apologize for being me but I do
apologize if you feel that I hurt you in some way. I say the same thing if I
anyone feels like I've hurt them too so that I've probably said some things
like inadvertently that I've had hurt people's feelings or I had over at Dwork's
because I'm not perfect and I've said things I regret too and it's like so I just ask that yeah
You know, I'm sorry and it's except my apologies
And that's not my intention. I'm my intention is to like you know really bring people together and have fun and it's like
it's way off track sometimes or
It was a little bit off course, but I do have
No, I do. I do love people. I love I love humanity. I'm a very Prometheus kind of energy
Prometheus loved humanity because he created humanity actually
With that I've seen that movie that movie scared me I was scared in that that movie
Amethias, yeah
That's not the story that
No, I'm not even at the great myth of a but that's the Prometheus movie. It's kind of based on that too
It's like
Yeah, basically Prometheus was
a Titan and then he actually stole fire from the gods because he created mankind
but he didn't like they were all like hiding in caves and in the dark if he had no fire
they're all cold they're off there they're eating raw meat and stuff like that
and he's like I want to bring them fire and this is like well if you bring them
fires are gonna be more powerful than the gods you know eventually come in this
storm Olympus and stuff
And so God forbid you give humans technology or education, right?
I guess we do sometimes though. It's like origin story is where the connections
Well, that's interesting too because um along with the issue they created
The first man that created like a written man's name that they created
There's adam and Christianity, but they also but then they had given away
All the animals, they gave away all the gifts to all the animals, but by the time they had man, they had no gift to give them.
And so they created a woman. And Pandora actually means hand means all, or they know all, and then Dora means gift.
So, Pandora means all gifts. So she was the first woman that she was in view with this by Hermes with a curiosity and a little bit of an ability to maybe see for something.
Always blaming the woman.
I know.
You're curious.
We're just curious kitties.
That's the point of it.
That's the whole point of it, is to, like...
If you give somebody a box, it doesn't happen to Psyche, too.
This is why you have to procreate.
Psyche had all these tasks to do for Aphrodite.
She was trying to get her approval to marry him.
The last task Aphrodite gave her was to go to Queen of Hell,
ask for a box of a little bit of her beauty,
and then bring it to Aphrodite.
Aphrodite could have it.
And then if you get it, and she's able to go through hell and dig up the bottom, and she's dead.
It's a little dated.
What is?
They didn't have VR headsets and AI scripts and stuff.
Yeah, this is an old myth though, but I'm saying so
Like he opens the box of beauty because she could not resist
She's like well
She's like she's like she's got her eyes have like a little crow speed on it and like she had her
Make the bill to smear all the work to running around to use cap
But she's like I'll just take a little bit of the beauty from the box
She opened the box, but I'll stand in the box with that. That's why she fell asleep
That's why it's called psyche awakens because keep it has to come down and wake her up
Oh, I didn't oh, okay. I get okay. I did not know that's why you went by a site. Okay. Thank you for explaining that
And also in the story, at one point in the story,
she's told to go find out what he looked like.
She told you the monster, and so she gets this oil lamp,
and she goes close to his face,
and some of the oil drips on his shoulder,
and he wakes him up.
So she awakens him at one point,
and then he awakens her later in the story.
So it's a very interesting story.
And he actually kicks her out of the view.
So she becomes a goddess by the end of it.
But the whole reason she was in trouble
is because she was so beautiful that they stopped worshiping
Uh-oh, Aphrodite got mad, she got mad, look at that.
Aphrodite's son is Cupid, right?
And so she said Cupid could go shoot Psyche with arrows
to make her fall in love with some monster,
but then he accidentally hit himself with one of the arrows,
and then she fell in love with her, and then she fell in love with him.
Interesting, but he's also known, he's known as kind of a rascally god, he's kind of like, he's like, he's, he's causing all this trouble to make him fall in love because of all the complexes from all this like infidelity and people sleeping and all this.
And so he caused a lot of trouble if he's kind of known as like a, kind of a devil in a group of all of these.
He's also one of the oldest gods.
was Eros, because it was like the desire of the lot.
Like, maybe he lost a little bit.
That's interesting.
And there's a cute thing.
There's a young cute bit, like a baby cherub-looking one,
but in psyche and cute bit, he's more of like,
he's like, get out there and leave it at home.
He's not the cherub.
I think that cherub is deceiving.
I think that cherub is a very, very old man,
and they're like, a baby body.
You know, it's so funny that you say that there's a guy in these communities known as BG
I always thought he looked like a little cherub and he has the personality of an old man even though he's young
I know BG. That's funny. Yeah, have you have you spoken to him extensively because you'll see what I mean if you do
Yeah, I mean I he was when I start I came on last year when I started doing
He was on you this panel. He really interrogated me about Lisa Georgana. That's his gift
That's that's his gift. He's a natural interrogator. He should work for CIA or the FBI
Yeah, yeah, he was good at it. But no, I think I was able to hold my own in his
interrogation. He's a little he's a little abrasive. I think that I don't know what his
back I always suspected he comes from a military family. I suspected that about him for a long time.
Um, very straight laced very matter of fact, but he he's like a little old man inside
He's he's like a grandpa, but
Like maybe he was raised by his grandpa. I don't know, but he's like a little old man
in a young guy's body
Yeah, I might show up again. I know he maybe he's mad at me or something like I don't know if he was like a big
I think of a ban on me, but maybe I didn't even get a long kind of but uh
He's one of those people I was like one of those straight guys. I was hitting on when I first hit the scene. Oh
Well, then he wouldn't like that because he's very he's very very conservative
But that's that's what I like. I like I like playing with those guys
It's fun for me. I bet you do. Yeah, but you do
I'm really harmless. I'm all talk. I don't bother. Someone's asking if I'm drunk. No, I'm a little intoxicated.
I'm probably a little dehydrated because I was running around today. I got into nature today. That was
something I needed to do and I'm still in nature. I'm outside even though it's there's electricity.
civilized people, me, at least me, and I feel particularly blessed at this moment.
I'm happy.
Good.
I'm happy too.
I'm happy.
I'm like, I have a smile on my face I can't like wipe off right now because.
Good. Good vibes here. Hey, did you see the Chris K thing or do you know about Chris K, right? I know about it and I know about him. You know, he does tarot too. I know. Do you know about that? He's done, he's read me. I had him read me when he first was coming out trying to do it. He was on a rumble. I don't dislike Chris K, but.
Chris K can be easily influenced and I don't want him to do anything to you
How I feel yeah, but hey knows I like him for the most part. I think he's a little
He doesn't always think before he speaks but a lot of us don't do that. That's fine. He's very
You know, there's a lot of erratic energy around him. He's he's very like
Yeah
Almost like static. He's like static
Indie static
like
Being from Riverside and like, you know kind of in that Riverside lifestyle
It's a little bit of a different world there, you know, it's a little bit more rural.
I can't remember right going a little bit of what, but this smells like cow, cow shits
the whole, trying to drive it out there, it's like, it just feels like cow, cow shits it.
Well, you don't want that, no, none of that.
You want to be, you want to, you want to be in comfortable, pleasant to look at surroundings
as much as possible.
I was reading some Marie Kondo what I put my lighter Marie Kondo you lost a lighter
yeah it's somewhere around here let's go look for it Marie Kondo wrote a book called the the art of
hiding up or something like that like you heard this book it's pretty good it's about how your
or happening if they have a good vote?
Well, your environment is a reflection
of how you feel inside, okay?
Not always, but it often is.
And like, I guess how I feel inside,
maybe the reason that I switch locations so much,
maybe a part of me does feel a little lost.
So I'm searching for something,
but even though I'm lost,
You're always going to see me in a pretty nice surrounding. I can guarantee that
but I
Have pretty much figured out where I want to be like long-term
And I'm going to build my home where I want to be long-term
Yes, well, here's a quote I like by her. She said, the best way to choose what to keep and what to throw away is to take each item in hand, one hand and say, does this spark joy?
If it does, keep it. If not, dispose of it. This is not only the simplest but also the most accurate yard object by which to judge.
You have to do that. Well, I'm a perpetual minimalist.
I grew up in a very, well, just too much materialism.
I grew up in that environment.
Yeah, just too much, too much, too much.
I don't want too much.
I was an 80s baby, and the 80s were all about, right?
It was like the yuppies, right?
Access.
It was like they're all about making the color and very, very motivated.
There weren't a lot of cocaine, I believe, too.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I mean, look, if you were going to be a co-head in the 80s with the early 80s,
because that's when it was pure, that's when it wasn't cut with all kinds of crap
that does end up killing people.
Our current president, he was a co-cat, I don't hear anyone says, he still might be, it's just a bit much.
Very, I mean, it's crazy how, like, oh, um...
Jamie, I think, turn up your sound. I think the sound is fine. Yeah, it's crazy how like, you know, how many, how much drugs are in, like, how many people are doing drugs, and like, how big a part of the culture is also, they're like, very much brought into the country, like, you know, with the government.
you're doing something just to be able to function and keep going at a very high
pace because it's very demanding but you shouldn't.
Also politicians I think are the most
compromise of any profession it's like I think they're all like you know I think
there's a shadow government that kind of runs things for real and they put all
these puppets on and the puppets have to compromise so they like they get all
these people like they're like is he blackmailed and they're they're making
politicians so they have something over them that they can easily hold what to do
and they'll do it right so
If you're a politician nowadays, you really are a true public servant, and you've got to really think about it if you're going to do it, because if someone doesn't like you, they're not only going to come after you, they're going to come after whoever you care about.
That's how it works.
Oh yeah.
That's a lot of them.
I wouldn't advise anyone to go to politics really.
Yeah.
Yeah, plus it's so polarizing where it's like remember how like popular Trump was in the country
I would love them and then I think it's going to be a politician like half people hate them
They say it's very polarizing
because you know politics is for you just these birds with two wings, right?
I think they both need one way you know both wings to like fly
But they're basically what on the same bird. It's not like a different bird and so
They're very much the same parties in a certain way, how they operate and things like that.
And we have this dual system all over the world too, but I think the dual system is
just like what's apparent.
The true system is like the one world, because we are one world, and we really are.
And we're just getting more and more into the one world, but I think we've had the NWO.
Well, the only way that we're ever going to get to meet the ETs is if we all
collectively
Agree that we're one world
I'm glad to hear that you agree, but a lot of people they don't they don't want one world
That's like one thing that could unite all of humanity, right?
They have an alien threat then all of humanity would see the UFO gets shot by the hellfire missile earlier
Oh, I heard about that
The shape doesn't make sense it's like
Like from um
What was that one bit flight of the navigator? It's like a sauce. Oh, yeah
But it's going the wrong way like it's going the like wide way into the the wind and it's just like
It gets hit.
They are here.
It gets knocked off.
It follows it.
It follows it like it's getting like a magnet or like a gravity manipulation magnet.
It's weird.
It's very weird.
But you should definitely watch it.
They're here.
It's crazy.
And then what happens to introduce that a political assassination happens right after this is released?
Yeah, what the well a lot of things have happened lately a lot of things
I mean they've been talking about the UAPs or UFOs
Wag the dog. It's a term you wag the dog
Look at this look at this look at this tail wagon
UFOs now
well
They want to
The beings are here. They're here.
Yeah, that's it. That's it right there. Watch this shit. Watch this stuff. Watch it get hit.
This is the, uh, this outside of Yemen. Watch it. It's gonna get hit by, it's gonna get tracked
and hit by a hellfire missile. And then watch what happens. It's so, look at that.
Now watch this stuff follow it. Look at that.
What the frick the guy the guy said what the web he literally said what the F is that?
Well, I mean here's the thing. I mean since I mean officially what the F is that what the F is that like
officially since the 50s, but realistically since
The beginning of time I'm gonna grab my food BRB
They have been here and
You know, I feel bad for the people who have had experiences and nobody believed them
That's the worst
but
Because even if it wasn't like really
You think that there's like actually really abducted or that it's like a oh, yeah
No, no physical physical sometimes maybe astral or spiritual or you know, some other energetic way, but it's physical. Yeah
I think that there's a lot of people walking around that are hybrids
All right, I have to do with that. Yeah, I think that
Normalize with the way we like a human beings and stuff like we're normalized like oh humans look like this
but they give out all the variation in the species like how different some people look and like
And also, I think the earth is kind of like a zoo for like the whole
Everything else is life from everywhere over here. We have such a variety of life here. It's like it's amazing
well, I mean
What people have to get more comfortable with is what the rudimentary form of human is
You know head to arms body to legs
able to communicate
able to be self-aware. That's human, right? But people are so wrapped up in things that
don't define what it is to be human. And it has to do with isolationism, people who have
separated or segregated themselves. You've got to understand that. I mean, look at how
You know, we look very different, and we're both human, but we're different genders, we're
on different areas of the spectrum, different heights, but for some reason...
It's like a pole, it's like the skin color is like, you know, it just varies from like
But it's basically on the same pole, it's not different, it's all hair, it's all skin,
it's all the same basic skin, it's all the same basic DNA, it's just those variations
of it, and based on different genetic things, and that's what's beautiful is the diversity
of the world, because we're all different but we're all the same too, we're all the
same in a certain way.
Someone in the chat is funny Jay Jay says wave them down get a free vacation. I'm trying
I'm trying to very hard very hard. I've you know
I've said for years that if they arrive as soon as they do there's gonna be one
He's gonna pick me up and take me on a trip. So I'm just waiting
I'm just waiting one of my favorite movies is a movie from the 80s called earth girls are easy. That's all about me
That is I'm just waiting for the hot alien. Where's Jeff Goldblum?
He knew
Yeah, it's debut. Oh
And look at mr. Big Pines
Busting in he knew about that. I'm eating a burger
Why with Jeff Goldblum? Oh, no, not not not I don't like that
Yeah, that's a bit nice. Yeah, I don't I don't I don't want to see that. I just want him to be a hot alien
I mean where I am right now. He could land right over there and
Say hey, baby. You want to go for a ride in my flying saucer? I'll be like, oh, yeah, let's go
I'm are I'm already ready. Like can I just drive my car up the ramp and?
You know show me the universe
Who's who's live stream is this?
Who's you think auto
Excuse me
It's auto remember auto for today. Yeah, it's honest line straight. No, it's like you miss this
It's mine
Why are you worried you're not wearing a shower and clothes out are you naked?
No, bro. I'm not naked bro. There's not wearing a shirt
No, bro. I got my shirt off man. Can you give me a quick flex? Can I have a quick flex auto?
You can't say with it. I'm trying to find out where I am.
Who's stream is this?
Okay, you see what this is? Psychey Awakens TV.
This is not Psyche.
What do you think I am? Do you see it says Psychey right here? Yeah, I brought you up, see?
Look, I'm gonna switch this right there.
No. Psyche?
Psych, okay, you're here, but this is not your stream.
Who's is it?
I don't know.
Don't argue with me, Otto.
I mean, come on, you're being very reasonable.
That's my stream.
Alexandra.
Yes, sir.
Alexandra, whose stream is this?
It's Psychi Stream, Psychi Awakens Terra.
I'll share with all of you all of our because we're all on right now. So it's all of ours
Broadcasting
Oh, am I for real I'm not a I I'm real
Alexandra
Otto
Where am I
Where are you you're in my phone?
You don't know where we are if you don't know where you are. How are we supposed to know where you are?
Most likely you're somewhere on earth. Um, are you are you in the United States or a different country?
Well, no, I'm trying to find out what's
You're on my stream auto auto look at the name on the stream. It says psyche awakens TV, right?
No, it says
It says be be be be that's the title of the stream is beat his biscuits, but no it's called thank you waking to the show
This is not yours. Come on, bro. Okay. I'm taking you off. Okay. Go away. Go away
He might he's having fun tonight, he's having fun doing something
That's what's happening most likely in his world
I'm having sativa right now at some point. I'll have some indica and I'll be in the my night. Yeah
And
And I got hard cider and I got this and all these things
Keep me sane. I've had a cigarette
Well, then don't start
If I if I was not in my own therapy world, I would not be doing that, but
Until I have to go and face my obligations
I mean, I like that third hit doing what I need to do
The the sense can kind of give it to me like
Whatever yeah, whatever autos on it very strong. Oh, he's back inside. Oh, yeah, he's he's really is tweaking for
Are you okay? You know where you are yet?
I figure it out. I figure it out. I'm
side channel
I don't lie
What was Alexandra doing? I am smoking legal sativa
And I am talking to three handsome gentlemen tonight.
And I'm having a good time.
What are you doing?
Thank you, Bob.
What are you doing all dressed up?
Are you home?
Are you at home?
I'm not.
I'm not dressed up.
I am okay.
Are you at home?
No, I don't live here full time. It's my walking to your car alone tonight, Alex
Well, my car is parked where I can see it and I won't be walking to it
I'll be going inside good and I'll go to bed at some point
Alexandra
I'm
42 years old. I'm home. So I got my shirt off
Okay
Well, I'm pretty I'm 46 years old. I will not be taking my shirt off
but
I'm glad you have your shirt off
There were many times in my life that I have my shirt off in public and I enjoyed it profusely
But now it's not that time
At all
There'll be that time later. Not not not on here not on you
Well, I didn't have some free calls, you know a few months ago. I was having some I bet you did. I bet you did
Auto can you show us your body a little bit?
What are you doing? Oh
I want one of your nipples to kind of-
Dude, come on, man.
Oh, wow.
So today auto- oh my god, today auto was interrogating me.
It's fucking gross, dude.
No.
He's in pretty good shape, look, for his age, yeah, he's in good shape.
He's like looking at his door to me.
No, no, he's in his 40s.
He's not going to work out every day.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, my God.
Alexandra.
Can I ask you something?
See, go ahead.
How tall are you?
Um five foot seven five foot seven. It's like pretty tired for it today.
Are you always, are you always very pleasant?
You're such a very pleasant woman. I hope you're all right.
Oh, I can be I can be a real the opposite. I can be a real BITCH. I can be a real bitch
But for the most part I try to be
You know nice
You're very pleasant. I think you're very pleasant. Thank you
I think I like the way that you sound. I think I like the way that you speak. I think I like the way
everyone loves her voice. I think I like the way you present yourself.
But you know what, thank my parents for that.
I take no credit when it comes to the physicality.
This is all my mom and my dad.
They did.
They put a lot of work into me to know how to act right.
Even though I deviate it from it.
Oh, Otto wants to see me.
Yeah.
Are you guys going to do a bid check, Otto?
OK.
He is.
Be quiet.
Let Alexandra stand up.
All right, Otto, only once.
And then never ask again.
You get one more.
I will never ask again.
Let's see.
Let's make it to where you can see me.
Hold up.
All right, I'm paying attention turn it that way. All right. Here's here's me. Oh my god
Not not too bad
Not too bad
Not too bad. Not too. Yeah
I'm all right, I'm all right. You got
Thanks, big pipes. Thanks. Thanks everybody. Look
Thank you. Thank you. If I can just get a little feedback on a occasion. Thank you psyche awakens for
Having a platform that built my ego up a little bit tonight
Everyone like the stream
subscribe
donate
Buy the merchandise. He's got everything
Alexandra make it happen. I will Alexandra Alexandra
I do have, I do have, I don't want to like announce, I am working on like, because I started
my, the book, the book that I ended up writing, I started it as like, I was going to just
do it as a report, right?
There's so much to put to it, so I actually ended up making the report.
Let's talk about it, let's talk about Trollopedia.
Yeah, well, I also need to think I have a new report coming out, which I'll give away for free and then it will
It's like kind of a preview of the book and let me see if I can
Pull up any pictures that people just need to get the book. I mean
It's five dollars everyone buy trollopedia. Please. It's if you just want to understand
What the lay of the land is?
the YouTube streets you're gonna buy the book it's good Alexandra Alexandra yes
I have you know you you flew you flew like an angel are you not scared of what
summer is going to say about that I like summer
Okay, but I like summer. I think summer summer and I
No, no, no summer and I we spoke behind the scenes and
We're we're at a good place and I feel that a lot of people probably would love to see summer and I go at it
but summer and I are actually
We understand each other because we went through something not too dissimilar from one another
But she's just a strong woman if you have a strong personality. I have a strong personality in a different way
She actually has a birthday very close to my mother's birthday. She told me today when she told me I was like
I'm really glad that you got an opportunity to talk because I know in my show there's a lot of energies and it's like if someone are like kind of stirring stuff up and stuff like that and it's like
Yeah
But whenever like people talk one-on-one it's like there's a different thing, it's like a different, so I was like I really wanted you guys to talk one-on-one
I knew that I'm really glad I had the opportunity to I gave her my email
So I hope that and she and she said, you know, so I hope I get to know her because she's doing some amazing things
When it comes to helping, you know young girls avoid
certain kinds of problems and trouble and whatnot
So I don't know. I don't know to know Alexandra
But like two months ago you flew like an angel
About two months. Well, thank you. Oh, thank you. I was very angelic. I was very angelic the way you did it
And very sexy
Very sexy. I was going for sexy. I wasn't going for angelic, but I'll take angelic because I
Would like to meet I think I have met a real angel before I think I have
But I would like to definitively know
The next time
That's what I want. I want something definitive
That's completely definitive that would be amazing because I like the Bible. It was in the Bible when they talk about the angels
It's amazing, and I'm sorry. I don't mean to over talk you. Let me try it out now
Definitely a woman definitely a woman
Well
Yeah, she definitely is but you know what I think in a previous life. I might have been a man
I think I think in a previous life
I may have at one point probably not the most recent one if there's such a thing
But I think at some point in time I
Most likely got to be male
Because I am very jealous of males because I feel like males
Have more fun
You know, I think you do. I don't think you want to admit it
But I think men have more fun
And plus on top of that as a man you have more consistency
Because as a woman, you know, you got your
cycle
That is what ruins everything, emotionally, physically, even when it comes down to things
that you want to do, it's like, oh my god, my god damn period's here.
You know, it's like, it's tough, but as a man, you don't have that.
Everything stays consistent.
You know a lot of women they're like, oh, no, I don't want menopause. I have been waiting
I would like menopause to walk up to me and say, okay
no more of
The issues and I would just be like, yes, hasn't happened yet
This is a biblically accurate
Yeah, I see that I don't think that's accurate
That's like an Ezekiel has these wheels, and it's like a, it's like a giant eye surrounded by these wheels, and that's kind of a, it's just, it's kind of a scary
someone where it's like an AI of it, but it's like an airplane and it's outside the airplane and flying around
Well, it's a, you have to, you have to think about the AI is trained on, and then
I guess I get down to that one, that one's better than like
The stuff I see is like at a
Conscious level is like a DMT trip. I guess I think that the angels can look any way that they want to look
You know, what's ever whatever it's comfortable or the person?
You know, I think that
Guitars you sound like an angel
Alexandra, I'm nothing but a dirty dog. I'm just a dirty dog, Alexandra. I'm just gonna put it to you this way
And I'm just gonna I'm just gonna let you know that I'm a dirty dog. I'm just a dirty
That's that's why you shouldn't say that about yourself. You shouldn't say that about yourself
Well, I'm a man
And I'm dirty and I'm dirty
Well, that's what men are supposed to be
really okay because not not all but as a guy at least you can get away with it
and you don't get in trouble
I had no idea. I had no idea that I came into this channel. I had no idea how I got into this channel
It's the guy with the good fitness advice
Yeah, there's a track you have
Untrackable you have really good fitness advice. I heard you
On psyche awakens the other night and you're saying that if people want it to be in shape
They have to live
what they want to look like. You were correct.
Dragable.
I look the way I live, that I used to live.
I think it's different.
Alex, he likes to go outside in his underwear, like go in the rain in his underwear.
He's been out on my street before.
Good for him. Good for him. He likes nature. So do I.
That's why I'm in nature right now.
It's bad.
Alexandra.
I'll just say it.
She hears you.
All right.
Alexandra, I like women.
I like nature.
Men are in nature, too.
Otto, what about me?
Well, that's the point that I like women. They're they're very they're very nature
There they are the basic of what is nature women are
Basics are auto likes everything
Alexandra what I'm trying to say Alexandra is that women are the roots of nature
The rule so Alexander I'm looking at you
I'm looking at you Alexandra, and I like you and I like you because thank you
And I like you and I also like you because he's gonna take you I
Thank you. I think you're part. I think you're part of nature. I think you're part of nature. I think you're part of I am
I think you're part of trees, I think you're part of the clouds, the sky, I think you're
very beautiful, Alexandra, I think you're very beautiful.
I appreciate very much.
Thank you.
I appreciate Gracia's.
I appreciate very much what you said, and I'm out of, right now I'm in a mental state
to where everything that you just said completely resonates.
do feel one with nature at this moment. Today I had a good day. I hiked, I didn't
get hurt, that's a plus, and I'm outside still right now. I'm talking to four
incredible minds
and I feel like you're sitting here with me right now and that's wonderful.
I'm not incredible, Alexandra, I'm not incredible.
Well, you're humble.
I'm just a dirty dog, I'm just a dirty one.
Well, you are, define yourself however you want,
but it's incredible that we're all here when you really think about just the element of probability.
You know what I cannot forget why you just fucking did five minutes ago.
You stood up and you flew like an angel.
I liked it so much.
Well, thank you. Yeah, thank you. Thank you. Thank you for saying that. I
Keep I keep thinking about why you did in my mind. I keep on
Rewinding and winding and winding and winding. That was fucking sexy. That's
That was fucking hot that was fucking jealous like he
I just wrote psyche he wrote you a song just now. He just wrote a song that the song lyrics could be like
oh you look so angelic and i'm rewinding and rewinding it in my mind
i'm gonna write the song right now could you just stand up one more time that could be the song
Very very insecure now. I understand now. I understand why
He shouldn't
Should be
I
Want to know Sam and I saw you guys talk to each other. No, I think he's saying summer
No, Sam. Yeah summer summer feels very oh summer
No summer is summer summer is fine when Alexandra when Alexandra is in the picture
She's just not used to me. She's not used to me. You have to get used to me
She's not used to me. She's she's gonna get used to me and I'm gonna get used to her and that's what it is
I'm I'm a little different and I know that I'm not just saying that I am very different and
Coming to peace with that
It's good
Making the song hold on a second making a song
Oh, he's making a song right now. Okay, we're watching Psyche in his laboratory. We're watching Psyche. We're watching the process.
Alexandra.
The process.
Lotto. Lotto.
I'm five foot one. I'm a very short man.
Well, then you got to have kids with somebody who's tall.
That's what that's what you gotta do if you choose to because you might you might choose not to have kids
If I need to
You know I like you a lot people are I like you I like you to auto I was listening to
Stream earlier, and I heard a lot of things that you had to say
To be honest, you're interesting
I wish I didn't have a language barrier with you. I wish I could speak fluent. I wish I could speak
No, no, no
I just know it would be different. It would be different
Yes, absolutely
Absolutely, the nuances would be different
Alexandra, I like your style. I like your style. Thank you
Yeah, thanks
Not a lot of people
That's why summer feels very very very afraid
That's why summer
But don't but let's not let's not talk about summer cuz she's not here
Summer just has to get used to me summer summer thinks well, I'm not gonna say what summer thinks
But summer has to be she has to get to know me
Summers are very sexy woman do it by the way. She is
She won the bikini contest. I'll tell you that that girl her body will not her body doesn't which that girl has a
body
like I just look and
I'm straight, but that girl has a body and then on top of that
On top of that her she has like a certain attitude that aligns with her physicality. She she's she's very
balanced
Nice, and if you yeah, she she is she's fiery, but she's balanced
And she's just when you talk to her and you you know, I had to
Let her kind of see that I'm not super fiery.
People think that I'm a little bit more fiery than I am
and I'm not.
I'm very, I'm like a,
Smoldering ember, maybe
Earth Angel. I'm Sagittarius Rising, but I found out my other thing. My other, um, do you sit down or something?
The other one is Aries and that that makes sense for me because
I'm, I'm a bit, um, aggressive when I need to be.
That's fine, you too.
I have the summary.
Alexandra, Alexandra, I'm Aquarius.
I'm Aquarius.
Oh, you're, you're an aerosome.
You know what's funny?
Um, summer is on the cusp of Capricorn in Aquarius.
You're Aquarius.
I'm a very interesting and a various Mars all in the first house
You're attracting you you're sorry you're you're attracting you
So that means well, do you know what that means that means that you're that you're what were you doing that before I?
I'm doing a lot more now like I have a you know
Yeah, I'm doing a lot. I think it's a lot more now like I'm meeting a lot of people that are
Very vibing with it my astrology. I have a lot of liver in my chart, but I don't have any water
Except my little thing Scorpio and that's kind of like black water, but uh, yeah, I don't I don't have any water or air
I'm all fire and earth
Okay
Yeah, yeah
That uh, it can be intense. I'm I'm I'm I'm exactly where I should be I got
Because I do like fire a lot. I'm not a pyromaniac, but I do like you know what?
I always wanted to learn how to do be a fire spinner. I
Always wanted to do that. I might do that
Hibis love that shit
Okay, do you remember the song?
I don't know, hopefully you can hear this, Alex.
I know you were having trouble hearing it before.
I don't know.
Is it Earth Angel?
Oh, wow.
piano in the beginning. Love it.
I can play this.
I love Sandra.
Every step of blessing
I like to go through the air
She lifts her eyes
The room begins to close
Wings unseen
But everyone walks
She stands up
The world slows down
She stands in a circle
She stands up
Lifts off the ground
Otto's heart beats like a drum in his chest
Caught in orbit
He knows he's the last
And yelling
when she spun that day
wow
white music is perfect
i like that part
dami
아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아, 아,
Thank you, Psyche Awakens, for bringing us into the future
of entertainment.
I mean, seriously, thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
But I mean, you're implementing all the tools on the fly.
creating this amazing atmosphere for all of us wherever we are.
You know, whenever I start my life through and always say good morning, good afternoon, good evening, whatever time it is, wherever in the world it is that you are.
We're all in different places in the world, but we're all hanging out.
And for someone who's a solo traveler like me, it means a lot. Thank you.
You do a lot to me too.
Thank you for everything.
I'm just blessed to know you and Pipes and Intrackable
and even Otto, I'm just a lucky guy.
And great vibes tonight.
Big Pipes was playing along to that song perfectly.
Big Pipes.
I can't wait to see what big I'm so glad you change your name the big pipes instead of what it was before
Thank God change it again. Oh, who are you now?
Oh, so you're somebody well don't say okay. It's a secret. Yeah, it's like the name I'm gonna go by okay
All right, well don't say you're not ready
I was thinking, I'm pouring a fat fricking shot here, though.
You drinking whiskey tequila or vodka?
Like the shittiest vodka. It's called Quality Times vodka.
Oh, sounds like a good idea.
Be careful. Be careful with the vodka.
Yeah, this shit is bad.
Yeah, be careful.
I'm going hard.
Can I get a more specific slide for a little bit?
Have you ever tried tequila with whiskey tequila?
That's a very popular in Los Angeles, Tito.
It's a very popular phone.
Very popular in California.
Yeah, it is.
Jose Cuervo, Tequila, and that's the East Coast.
I don't know about what people drink out here.
I love the silver, oh, the trunks.
I love the trunks.
Dude, I can't believe this.
Do you like the big trunks of silver?
Wow.
Hey, Jay, how are you going to chat?
Did everyone like that song in chat?
I think that was good.
So when is psyche Palooza gonna happen? We got it. I want to meet y'all in person so bad
You have no idea. I want there to be
psyche awakens Palooza
sometimes
I mean, I'm I'm right here. I'm uh, you know, I'm a pretty open schedule because I can't
Never you can't
Well, I probably I'm going to pop it before I leave Cali. I am gonna pop in most likely to psyche's area
I'm not seeing any dates. I don't want anyone to get crazy and try to do anything to me or anything
But before I leave here. Yeah
Just to say hi
Are we still here you guys you guys gotta make it fancy you have fancy it up or so no no no no
because I actually want to
It's not gonna be fancy it's not gonna be fancy it's just gonna be
meat and greed
Yeah, I think I think it's gonna be more fancy because here's what I gotta do I gotta
go back to
I got to go back to Texas, I got to go check on my family on the east coast, and then I
get to be back out here full time towards the beginning, either the end of this year
or the beginning of this year.
Already I've been out here probably longer than I should have, but I've been spoiling
So, but before I leave here, I will, if psyche and I will talk to you, you know, or all, you know, DM you just to make sure that you're free and clear.
If you're not, you know, sweat off.
You know, I'm not, I'm not going to push myself into anyone's life anymore because I feel like I've done that before and people don't like that.
I don't think I don't feel like I'm going to visit. I'm going to visit for a day and we're going to
hang out at the pier. You said there's like a pier near you and it's going to be fun.
That's what we're going to do. I think that the purpose of the trip is that there's a whole
We're gonna do we're gonna do a grocery shopping trip for high-calorie foods for you
Yeah
You know what you you don't have to eat it, but I'm you're at least gonna have the option to have the high-calorie foods
For you know, however long the foods last because
Thank you. I want yes, that's gonna be the purpose of
The outing of the get-together meetup, whatever you do that with that Tilla you're making on
Yeah, I did I did I did people don't remember that but yeah
I had to fix him a little bit because he was having some problems. That's when we first talked
Yeah, well, that's how I met you and a lot of people
Really, it was all because of him because um
When I learned about the communities and everything that was when because actually it was he and I together
Who came up with the idea of doing the wikis?
Everyone is like oh
Wiki girl. She's just it wasn't it was not initially
It wasn't he was so that was like, oh does the community have a wiki and he was like no
But there needs to be a wiki. I actually remember promoting that
Yeah, yeah, but I pulled it because you know people people are very sensitive though
It's like okay, y'all really hate the wiki so much, you know, but yeah, that's
but Attila
He I had to
Like nurse him back to health because it was so bad. Do you remember? I don't know what happened
I'm sure you're by Homeland Security or something. He's like detained by I well
He's made some bad choices
I mean, it's like I don't know what he did
He last time I talked to him personally like Jose Sanders was over at my house
And then he like called yeah, and he was with jewel. You know, it's crazy. It's crazy
Jose Sanders gets around
He hung out with Trisha also. Do you know about that? Yeah?
Yeah, Jose gets around. He's everywhere. He hung out with the chicken Andy that weekend
But chicken Andy is like totally blue. I'm like what a fucking little prick bitch
Well chicken Andy's weird
I thought it's too too big for Jose San. Yes. Yeah
Yeah, I know him very well actually
Yeah, I know very well. I know that whole situation too well when I think about it, so we're not gonna talk about
Not today. Hey, Aldi. Oh, Aldi's in the
Oh God
Well, that was when he was halfway healthy that's when he was healthier
Yeah, I think they're playing this like you see that yeah, there's a drug movie
It was about like the crack cocaine epidemic, but they had this guy named the white boy
He was like this is his 14 years of police informant, but then he went to work selling crack for the
Gangsters in New York. He actually got like a life sentence for
He's had murders and everything get out before him and stuff like that and history is a white boy
But yeah, there's good times in the video they have like
So what's going on with you untrackable
I'm tracking you right now
It's okay, but it went very well, and I hope people are as good as me.
You have a really, you have a good speaking voice, intracable.
It's very distinct.
Very genuine, too.
No, I have a roadside page just like the old ones.
I can't find a good time to play.
I wonder who made that.
It was funny, it was like someone dancing and then it was like a good time to play.
But I don't think Good Times likes me very much.
Yeah, I wish people were like in the community were like...
He doesn't like anybody.
Yeah, he does.
No.
He likes women.
He's always thankful for women, I suppose.
No, he actually doesn't like women.
No, he actually doesn't.
Praying on vulnerable women.
Yes
Good times watch is you psyche I can tell
I know he's scared of you he's scared of you
I well mr. Big Pipe's miss the times better than I do probably
and Crystal does also, but I know him pretty well.
You would be very intimidating to him.
But he's gonna come around at some point.
He's studying you right now.
He's a worm, he's a coward worm.
Like most of these people really are like coward worms.
He's studying you though.
He's probably watching right now
and he's pissed on telling you.
that
He's studying you
And I'm gonna do something because I haven't talked about good times in a long time. Have I?
No, I haven't he wants me to but I haven't no no, but he likes to say oh
Alex is talking about me. Oh my god
Alex is making a clip of video. I haven't done that in a long time
So, he would be a little, what about me?
I'm good times.
Where's my good times?
Of course, in July, I think Aldi was like,
he would go funny or something up about having a good time stop
or good stock, you know, a good stock and good stock.
And he was like, they're selling to get a good house.
And he was like, when he started to get on stream,
and I thought that was like, if you want to come down here.
Jay, I was in love with who I wanted him to be, not
who he is, who I wanted him to be.
And he fed into my idea for a little bit.
He did.
Cheers.
Well, you know what?
Like if you know about the Anima and the Animas, the Anima is like the male's inner female and then the Anima is like the female's inner male but the Anima is always like there's usually just one of them and the male will project it out.
But in women, the Animas is like many different men.
And it's like, and it's like.
Yes.
It's really interesting, but oftentimes the onymus or the onyma can get projected out onto other people
And so it's like, you know, especially the men especially will project the onyma out because they like to repress their feminine side, right?
And so people project it onto a woman and they'll think that these qualities which are actually their inner qualities are the qualities of the woman
because the woman will be like a blank canvas in a way for sometimes like some of them have this fairy-like nature where it's like it's kind of
They can have these projections upon them and it's like and then the man ends up thinking that
Yes
Somebody else, but it's actually his own and it's like once the man can
The only bad thing is that it sometimes will come out the femme fatale or like
Like a negative like a shadow type animus like you know, there's
There's positive and that's why
That's why female actresses have a very difficult time
Because if you're an actor and actress by nature, you do absorb and take on the energies around you to play the part.
But if somebody knows that you have a high level of that capability and if they're manipulative enough, they can draw that out of you longer than you as the vessel.
Are prepared to handle that's happened to me before I
Will never date anybody who is a
Director again
Yeah
Yeah, you know as as women we have to be careful with that, but as men
You have to be careful. I mean, I I think I shouldn't just say as women when I think about it. It's a universal
concept
Definitely
Definitely, I gotta tell you the moon is huge tonight. The moon is freaking
I'm looking forward to it not being a full moon because where I am when the moon gets less bright
You can see all the stars and I and that's part of the reason why I'm here because I love looking at the stars
That's what I'm gonna invest in is a really good
Travel telescope. I've got to do that
Because I do like looking at you know, whatever I can possibly see in the sky
You gotta get it
one is like I don't need the best but but something something they're like very
compact okay I want something compact insane optical like better than
telescope pretty much I need something like that I need something like that for
when I go really because
Slowly, but surely I'm gonna get more and more remote. That is the bowl. I
Like I just saw a person using that camera to like get crazy shots of area 51
I want to go, I'm telling you all, whenever you're ready to do a group trip, I will be there, I want, but if we go, you know who has to come, Mr. Big Pice, Crack-a-dawn.
Yeah, I'll push him through his paces real quick.
Yes, I'll be.
He's got to at least commentate on the damn thing because we we should we should if I could have my dream
He'd make it like 30 seconds and be puke in it. I'll stop that
Well, I mean fitness
I don't know if it's a real crack-a-donna, but there's a crack-a-donna fan in my chat, but then I went over to his show, the crack-a-donna...
There's only one crack-a-donna, there's no other crack-a-donna, but crack-a-donna.
He's the only one.
In the chat though, I don't know if they can check.
It's him. Nobody else is impersonating him.
He wants people to think that people are impersonating him, but nobody else is impersonating crack-a-donna, but crack-a-donna.
He's awesome when it comes to the aliens, he knows about him.
I'd be cool, I would like to talk to him.
I'm going to try to become a member of a show.
It's kind of like an interesting show.
He has interesting eyes or hollow eyes or black eyes.
I don't know how he does that.
Pretty cool.
You see that, right?
I've always thought Krakadot has a nice face. I don't know why people are like
But even with even without the eye filter he has very intense eyes he has very
Very like very loose with like every other like
bold fat white dude ever I
Don't think that I think he's unique. I I don't think that I I actually
I don't like before you say they all look alike
I have not said they all look alike. I've never said that about anybody have yeah
When I was talking about who who have I said you said that to me you're like are you implying that like all?
White bald men look alike
Like maybe well then I was joking. I don't think all white ball and look like I don't think
All right, and then what they get beards like they'll grow beards, too
And then they all I look sometimes well not everybody should have a beard
Okay, some people are way better with beard some people are not it's just
It depends on like percent whatever your look is
Go for that look if you if you don't if you if you have a week
But listen if you have a week chin and you can it's that by growing a beard
No, actually psyche you don't have a week chin
You do not have a weak chin. You have a very good you have a you know who you look like I thought about it
William DeFeau
No, he looks like Hugh Jackman. That's who you look like psyche jack
I'm gonna send him some side brands
A combination of Hugh
your combination of Hugh Jackman
Jim Carrey
With a little bit of Jeff Goldblum maybe a dash of Howard Stern
Right, that's you. Actually, I took a picture on chat TPC has a thing where it's like you can put your picture up
And I'll tell you what it looks like
Fire fires that's on their new victim. Why do I have to be your victim?
We'll need to be so big they had to cut it out of the thing because it was like making the test
Audience is uncomfortable because his dick was so big.
Alex, when I went to the, I said who do I look like, and this is what they brought up.
But, no, I, I, I didn't, I didn't think it was the hair, but I love canneries, look,
I love canneries, I am, I, I, look, the last guy that I was kind of talking to knew that
I love canneries and he played into that, which was really fucked up when I think about it.
Yeah, I got to love his motorcycle section.
I have always wanted a canneries, I, I would be so happy.
I really would, but it's not the only type.
Alright, look up Countery's favorite motorcycle, and I have Countery's favorite motorcycle.
If I had to pick, I would say Matrix Keanu would be for me.
Keanu is favorite motorcycle I have.
It's 1974.
Yeah, not the vampire Keanu.
And maybe I don't like Hano as much as I think I do and I run like as I'm sitting here thinking about it
I maybe I'm just used to saying yeah, I look because that's always been my go-to
Hano or Wesley's Knights
Those are my two
Architites see like I would be careful man. I'd be like, you know you want to talk about Norton's and play music, dude
But it's rock out
Yeah
He plays guitar and he likes Norton.
You might be drunk, firefighter, but I'm drunk right now, and I'm having a good time.
You know what kind of bike I want I want a triumph. That's gonna be but I'm trying to get
They're all English bikes. They're owned by the same company called B. S. I
And actually I didn't have a BSA has a BSA stamp on the rear fender
So it's trying to you know, it's not big bikes knows everything about motorcycles and motorbikes. He's like a really
knowledgeable person
Yeah, I've heard of it you know, I never really read I know like there's like actually shagua vera had a Norton to
And that that one book thing he did the big
I agree, Jay. I have to get better on the scooter before I get a motorcycle. I'll die.
It's one of the bikes I've been working on over the years. It was a 1974 Norton 850 Commando.
I used to date a guy who rode a Triumph, and he did teach me how to ride his motorcycle.
It's pretty much like a Triumph, but it's like faster.
But yeah, every woman should date a guy who rides a motorcycle at some point in their life.
Every woman should, because it's something about that.
There's like the romance, the hotness, you know, it is a little bit of a guy overcompensating
Oh, there's no overcompensation for like balance. Well, it did for some minutes
Well, may for like a heart if I was like dressing up and leather and like riding a fucking like slow as well
Mr. Big Pikes, you know, like everyone knows
Like I will forever have a crush on Mr. Big Pikes and I'll explain why the reason why is because the first time
I learned about Mr. Big Pikes. He made this video
And he was on his motorcycle. He had the phone facing toward him
Hair blowing in the wind got the little slot and pepper in the beard had the bandana that the sunglasses on I was like
What the fuck is this?
Yes
Yes, because I I do have certain
And Mr. Big Pipes knows that about me. He knows that
He forever gets forgiveness because of certain things about him, which is a shame. I should not be that way. I am too superficial
I got to work on that bad Alex
Big places mischievous as fuck that's what it comes down to is a mischievous person
But he has a kind heart. I know that about
The wind died down
It's finally good.
Bye, attractable, attractable instructor.
Oh, okay, calm down and chat auto, auto is just in chat while I'm out, auto.
That's what that video that you made of may remind me of, dream weaver.
You know, I, for some reason, whenever I think about you, I think of the song Valentine by Belinda
Carlisle. Ooh, I've never heard that one.
That is what I think of when I think of you, Mr. Big Pikes.
Should I take this shot? Oh, it's fucking
This is my last one like this is a pint gun
My tolerance is at least a little I'll do half of it
Okay, I just have a couple
Yeah, I really am looking forward to this
I think the three book I'm putting out,
I'll show you like a couple of books on that.
Okay.
Let's see.
Yeah, I don't see it, okay.
You made, okay.
Hey, Psyche, Psyche, do you know of MC Frosty?
I've heard of him, I've heard of him, yeah.
I don't know if he's, yeah.
I want you two to me, I want you two to talk.
because he is, I think it, okay, Krakadon is smart, but MC Frosty is truly, in my opinion, the most intelligent person within the...
I think Frosty is more intelligent than Krakadon.
Yeah, he's quiet, he's quiet intelligent.
But super you're so dumb mystery big pipes, and then I destroyed him right right times in a row
He's like but I want to see frosty has like
MC frosty is very
emphatic
very
considerate
like self-aware
But he's a freaking genius. I mean I don't know who's smarter and see frosty or gamble when I think about it
It's hard to figure that out and their friends
It's but psyche needs to needs to get to know both of those men when I think about it
Sorry, I wouldn't love for him to meet those two. I would like site. Yes, sir. Hi
This woman for real is this woman is this woman the same way all the time and I'm talking about you Alexandra
This is really
And she's very real for me right now.
Ask Mr. Big Pies.
I was in love.
I was in sweet love.
All right.
As long as I've known her, she's been up to me
often, often.
I'm lucky to be able to meet y'all fairly.
I love it. I love it. I love it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, that's how he communicates.
Stop it.
That's how he is.
Why is the music?
I want to listen to Alexandra.
I'm going to say in Spanish.
Otto, here's what I'm going to do.
Otto, I'm going to do a stream just for you.
If you calm down right now.
on my channel I'm gonna I'm gonna do a stream all about you because you're
interesting and I could talk about you for at least two hours non-stop if I
wanted to so and it's gonna be a stream just for you
no no no I could do that I'll do that for autumn
getting in the way and I wanted to hear Alexandra and the music was getting in the way
No, it's not. It's fine.
Mr. Big Pots is going to play the blues for y'all tonight.
Mr. Big Pots wants to play his harmonica.
That is how Mr. Big Pots-
So, Psyche started getting me into f***ing little auto jobs.
I didn't meet you. I didn't meet you. I just took you. I went down a little bit.
It goes on all the way.
Yeah, so now you're like-
Shut the fuck up with the big pipes. Okay. I know I know who the fuck don't be mean don't be don't don't be mean to
Mr. Big Pipe's don't be mean to him
All right, I won't be but he's a nerd
But he's a nerd. No, he's not
Well, so am I I think all of us are we're all nerds on here who grew up
Actually, that's who we are. There is there is not a drop of nerd in me
There's a lot of nerd in me. It's everywhere. I'm so nerd that I'm nerd to the 10th power
Well, I think
I'm a nerdillionaire
Is there is that oh my god someone should someone should make a business nerdillionaire
Someone who's a nerd who wants to be a billionaire a nerdillionaire nerdillionaire
nerd
Nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, nerdy, ner
Man, there's a fucking women that can be fucking nerdy, but they're fucking sexy about it
Yes
Sexy about it. All you do is work with her pair of thick glasses
That's what I'm saying exactly. It's just put on the glasses. Yes. Just put on the glasses
She might be a fucking nerd, but she's sexy about it
She knows but see because you're because it's but you know what women feel the same
Okay, let's think about the Clark Kent superman's dynamic
You know
Yes, I mean that right there. Yeah, everybody
Everybody loves that. I mean even
Even if you think of like most of the superheroes, you know, Peter Parker
Who was Peter Parker?
Spider-Man
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he was a nerd who you know found his inner
strength
but
Most most sexy women are very smart. You know who you know who's impressed me
Pamela Anderson I
Have you noticed? She's not wearing her, you know, glam look anymore, but she's she is making a comeback right now
It was unbelievable this whole thing with Liam Nielsen. She's been in some movie roles lately again
That guy that she was with who she had her kids with he held her back. I always knew he did
Tommy Lee
Yeah
I'm a man. I'm Hispanic
I'm fully blooded his panic in my veins. Okay, you will find you will find his panic
100%
That's what you're gonna find in 100% is panic
You so okay. I got so I got that rhythm. So I got the rhythm. I got to read
I know about the Latinos don't don't you know, I got you don't got to tell me about it
I was in Florida. Look, I was I spent all my teens and 20s in South Florida. I know the Latino man
Trust me. I have a nephew who's half Latino. I
Know about Latinos the Latinos
are sexy men without a doubt.
Even if it's like the least sexy Latino,
he's still gonna be sexy.
It's just ridiculous.
It's the culture.
It's in the genetics.
Latinos for the most, Latinos, Hispanics,
do tend to be pretty multiracial
even though they define as Hispanic or Latino.
You got a lot.
going on and in that gene pool and um
Yeah, I mean you can't look I just had the biggest crush on john cicada. Do y'all remember john cicada?
He had the song just another day without you
Oh, well, I'm I'm
Okay, well, I'm older than you are so that's probably
I'm
Oh, you're 40
No, I'm 46
I'll be 142
142 not that much older than me
Okay, I'll give you that
I'll give you that but yeah, John Cicada and maybe I know about John Cicada because I was in South Florida
And I was around a lot of Colombians
resilience
Cubans Puerto Ricans
What else is the major group down there Argentinians
Peruvians
Who else you got?
It's a lot of people the only reason why I'm letting you talk is because I like you otherwise
I would have cut you off a long time ago
Okay
How are the kiddies doing
How are the cats?
Those cats they are they're going wild tonight they're they're coming around they want to hang out with you tonight
Like he is like a cat look like a house like he moves he moves a little bit like a cat. He's a little cat like
I'm sorry
And there's
I see her I'm looking I'm looking at I'm looking at your cats on like my iPad. It's bigger
Yeah
I got three cats. I think really the most here. Oh here comes another one. How many do you have four four?
Or I've ignored Lola and tricks but like Lola's tricks is mom. She had a lot of fear and then I know that there's
They're saying that the cats are becoming aware of social media. I
Don't know like do you think so? They're saying it. I was reading the article about it. It was in the Washington post
Like they were talking about there's cars or something becoming aware of
technologies
Well, people are reporting people are reporting that the cats are figuring out how to activate things
using the iPad or the foe
So
If your cats start
posting
I'm gonna know. I'm gonna know what happened
Alexandra, I'm 42 years old. I'm single. I have no kids
Well, that's great. I mean, are you are you looking to meet a woman because I know a lot of women who would probably like you I
Do well, are you looking are you looking for? Yeah, are you are you?
Well, are you exclusive? Are you exclusive to women? Are you looking for men too? Like like what's going on?
I'm exclusively looking
I'll leave it at that
He was asking about my penis a lot today, but um, well, it's okay. Oh, I mean
It's fun. He's like he's any tricked me because he was like, oh, I want to know how big it is and stuff like that
He's like, I'm interested and then I play and then he said, oh, I was just checking. I was one of the women to hear how
Tricking yeah, I'll be right back. I gotta I gotta switch phones again because my battery this thing sucks up the battery
I'll be right back. Okay
okay move a little yeah so i'm gonna try to kind of hit my green screen so i can get my green screen
bro that's an interesting woman right there i think she's a very interesting woman right there
hmm, sama, sama, sama, sama, now I can see why, now I see why, this is the first time
I see Alexandra, and this is the first time I see how Alexandra behaves, and now I see
Got it
Got it. I don't think we need the old, you know, it's not a competition
It's like no, bro. Let's go. Hey, hey Alexandra. Hey yo, uh, hey yo, hey yo psych
Yeah, that woman that woman Alexandra. I think she fucking got it going on
She got it going on
That's right. That's what I think. That's what I think. I think she got it going on bro. That's what I think, bro
she got it going on bro i like her style i like her f***ing the way she talks i like
her f***ing appearance i like the way that she handle handles herself bro yeah
and now i see why sama and now i see why sama feels threatened threatened now i see what
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I think alexandra has a lot of love to give
For real
I'm not playing, for real
I'm kind of like, I'm not in shock because
After all, I'm 42, but I am kind of, kind of in shock, in a way, in a sense, in a sense,
in a sense that, that, that was, Alexandra doesn't even have to try.
She doesn't even have to try.
She doesn't even have to try
It seems to me that she doesn't even have to try. She's just a folk all the dirt
And
That shocks that shocks a little bit that kind of shocks a little bit
Got it on I like
How do I convince me I
Like it. I like I like the shock. I like the shock
Shit, here we go.
I got my green screen, guys.
Fix that a little bit.
There.
Shit.
Hold down.
There, I got a green screen up.
Okay, see that?
Hold on.
There's my green screen.
Look what it does.
Just some special stuff.
I need to fix one side of it.
Okay.
Yeah.
What?
See the green screen?
Yeah, what what does it do?
What the green screen does is
It put images up on it like this
Like you'd see like that. Okay. I go like this. I can go add image or a visual effects, and I go have a green screen
And I need to fit up to bring up there you go
See
I do like that.
Yes.
Can you put any poster on it? Let me see how I can fix it.
Nice nights.
Thank you.
There.
Let's see.
Ah, fuck it.
There we go.
Let's stretch it out.
Pretty cool, huh? Yeah
There you go
And then I can also I can also do a full background like this like this you go how do I do it I guess
We'll just do the whole thing yeah do the whole thing, but I like when it just goes on the green screen though
There's like a poster, huh?
No, it is nice. It's nice
It's nice, especially especially the one the one that you have on right now. It is very
Romantic
No, it's very romantic. I think it's very romantic and I like it so I
Like it very romantic very crispy
I don't know, maybe I just don't want to take it to the right, but like, I'm gonna keep trying.
That works, that works better.
Okay, well...
Nice nights.
Nice night. It's very nice. I know it's not perfect, but I need to fix it a little bit.
Cool.
Okay guys, let's see. What time is it? It's uh, oh, it's actually 10, it's 11 p.m. Okay? It's a little early.
A little bit, but yeah, I'm thinking of
It's two AM in London, Ontario, Canada.
Yeah. Oh, there we go.
Oh, wow.
There we go.
Ladies, are you single or no?
Two AM in London, Ontario, Canada.
Two AM.
That's cool. You like that right there?
That's pretty cool.
What's that?
Yeah, bro. Pretty cool.
How's everyone doing in the chat?
What would she say, IP2?
She's not coming back, she said.
What, this time she's not coming back?
Well, I don't understand.
I'm blocking her chat now.
For the first time she blocked me her chat,
so obviously she's really, really hate me now.
But I'll play the beat of the song again. Hold on.
Sight.
Ha, ha, ha.
Hey!
Oh!
Crumble like a cookie when the heat's on stage
Beat a business biscuit, still a-sittin' in the cage
Talk tough online, but the flavor don't last
Snap like a cracker when the panel talks fast
Hook beaters, biscuits, dry and bland
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
Claim you bring spice, but you bring in regret
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
You came to the kitchen, but forgot the recipe
Crumbs while I feast on legacy on the fire in the oven you the smoke that won't stick your dough
Don't rise cuz you're game too quick
Peter's biscuits dry and bland no butter no jam just dust in your hand
Clean you bring spice, but you bring in regret
Panel got receipts. We ain't finished yet
Panel verse feast we don't starve on lies your plate got nothing but re-hated fries
I'm the main course true served hot. You're the snack that ever
when the heat's on stage.
Beet, huzz, biscuit, stale, left sitting in the cage.
Talk tough online, but the flavor don't last.
Snap like a cracker when the panel talks fast.
Hook, beat us, biscuits, dry and bland.
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand.
Claim you bring spice, but you bring in regret.
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet.
You came to the kitchen, but forgot.
Your dough don't rise cause your game too quick
Beat his biscuits, dry and bland
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
Claim you bring spice but you bring them regret
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
Welcome to real life
Alexander thank you thank you mr. Bigpipes thank you auto thank you everybody
thank you rando for the donations thank you everybody participating you can go
check out psycheawakens.com if you'd like to book a private reading I want to
say thank you I love you guys okay I will be back and maybe tonight maybe maybe
later I have to figure out some stuff I'm looking on some stuff and so
I'm gonna be working but I love you guys. Thank you
You have a great night guys
Bye guys
You have a good night
of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight crowds came running just to see the flame but
envy was the price of fame and now he stands where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every